[('Said Jammal', 'PERSON'), ('20 years', 'DATE'), ('Nigerian', 'NORP'), ('The 2010s', 'DATE'), ('the 2020s', 'DATE'), ('Premier League', 'ORG'), ('Bobby Madley', 'PERSON'), ('Karen Gillan', 'PERSON'), ('Jumanji', 'GPE'), ('BBC News', 'ORG'), ('Caribbean', 'LOC'), ('2019', 'DATE'), ('Israeli', 'NORP'), ('Benjamin Netanyahu', 'PERSON'), ('Gary McLaren', 'PERSON'), ('New Year', 'EVENT'), ('Paris', 'GPE'), ('Bastille', 'GPE'), ('BBC Sport', 'ORG'), ('Syrian', 'NORP'), ('hundreds', 'CARDINAL'), ('thousands', 'CARDINAL'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('more than 80 million', 'CARDINAL'), ('Marc Veyrat', 'PERSON'), ('Michelin', 'GPE'), ('Liberate Hong Kong', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE'), ('2020', 'DATE'), ('year', 'DATE'), ('Manchester United', 'ORG'), ('Ole Gunnar Solskjaer', 'PERSON'), ("Mason Greenwood's", 'PERSON'), ('Romelu Lukaku', 'ORG'), ('Inter Milan', 'ORG'), ('August', 'DATE'), ('The British Medical Journal', 'ORG'), ('more than 180,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('The Office for Students', 'ORG'), ('Four', 'CARDINAL'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Moore', 'PERSON'), ('Most decades', 'DATE'), ('the 2010s', 'DATE'), ('Theo Van Eijck', 'PERSON'), ('Dutch', 'NORP'), ('1964', 'DATE'), ('Libya', 'GPE'), ('South African', 'NORP'), ('MTN', 'ORG'), ('al-Qaeda', 'ORG'), ('Taliban', 'ORG'), ('Arsenal', 'ORG'), ('the Premier League', 'ORG'), ('Man City', 'GPE'), ('Leicester', 'GPE'), ('Aston Villa', 'GPE'), ('Burnley', 'PERSON'), ('months', 'DATE'), ('Moon', 'PERSON'), ('2020', 'DATE'), ('the year', 'DATE'), ('a year', 'DATE'), ('Jose Mourinho', 'PERSON'), ('Southampton', 'GPE'), ('Iraqi', 'NORP'), ('Adel Abdel Mahdi', 'PERSON'), ('More than 20', 'CARDINAL'), ('thousands', 'CARDINAL'), ('Andy Neal', 'PERSON'), ('Jiankui', 'ORG'), ('Pole Robert Kubica', 'PERSON'), ('Williams', 'PERSON'), ('2019', 'DATE'), ('Alfa Romeo', 'PERSON'), ('the 2020 season', 'DATE'), ('Boeing', 'ORG'), ('Starliner', 'PRODUCT'), ('2019', 'DATE'), ('Sintra', 'ORG'), ('Quinta da Regaleira', 'PERSON'), ('Portugal', 'GPE'), ('Knights Templar', 'PERSON'), ('Ayia Napa', 'PERSON'), ('Hong Kong', 'GPE'), ('Chile', 'GPE'), ('the Middle East', 'LOC'), ('Tom Brook', 'PERSON'), ('10', 'CARDINAL'), ('the year', 'DATE'), ('Yael Aflalo', 'PERSON'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('California', 'GPE'), ('Sudan', 'GPE'), ('BBC Sport', 'ORG'), ('January', 'DATE'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('Wednesday', 'DATE'), ('Premier League', 'ORG'), ('Manchester City', 'GPE'), ('Everton', 'GPE'), ('20 years', 'DATE'), ('the London Eye', 'ORG'), ('the turn of the year', 'DATE'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Dan Roan', 'PERSON'), ('2019', 'DATE'), ('kofun', 'NORP'), ('Japan', 'GPE'), ('Tudor', 'PERSON'), ('Elena Ferrante', 'PERSON'), ('Saudi', 'NORP'), ('Mancunian', 'NORP'), ('this year', 'DATE'), ('Infowars', 'ORG'), ('2012', 'DATE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Benjamin Netanyahu', 'PERSON'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Victoria', 'GPE'), ('The year', 'DATE'), ('2019', 'DATE'), ('2020', 'DATE'), ('Brighton', 'GPE'), ('Chelsea', 'ORG'), ('One', 'CARDINAL'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Japan', 'GPE'), ('Mikel Arteta', 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Arsenal', 'ORG'), ('first-half', 'DATE'), ('Manchester United', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Tech', 'PERSON'), ('this year', 'DATE'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Supreme Leader', 'ORG'), ('Baghdad', 'GPE'), ('Peter Wright', 'PERSON'), ('Michael van Gerwen', 'PERSON'), ('the PDC World Darts Championship', 'FAC'), ('Alexandra Palace', 'FAC'), ('the year ahead', 'DATE'), ('Bel Jacobs', 'PERSON'), ('Prof Paul Ewart', 'PERSON'), ('69', 'DATE'), ('New South Wales', 'GPE'), ('Victoria', 'GPE'), ('thousands', 'CARDINAL'), ('NBA', 'ORG'), ('30 years', 'DATE'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Poland', 'GPE'), ('Nazi', 'NORP'), ('World War Two', 'EVENT'), ('New South Wales', 'GPE'), ('3 January', 'DATE'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Maria Sharapova', 'PERSON'), ('the Brisbane International', 'FAC'), ('2019', 'DATE'), ('Earth', 'LOC'), ('Chinese', 'NORP'), ('New Year', 'EVENT'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('M Ilyas Khan', 'PERSON'), ('a year', 'DATE'), ('Kashmir', 'LOC'), ('Pakistani', 'NORP'), ('two dozen barrels', 'QUANTITY'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Ben Stokes', 'PERSON'), ('World Cup-winning year', 'EVENT'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('2019', 'DATE'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('200', 'CARDINAL'), ('30%', 'PERCENT'), ('Manchester City', 'GPE'), ('Pep Guardiola', 'PERSON'), ('Premier League', 'ORG'), ('Liverpool', 'GPE'), ('Cissoko Embalo', 'PERSON'), ('West African', 'NORP'), ('Fallon Sherrock', 'PERSON'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('season', 'DATE'), ('Premier League', 'ORG'), ('Peter Wright', 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('PDC World Championship', 'EVENT'), ('7', 'CARDINAL'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Michael van Gerwen', 'PERSON'), ('2019', 'DATE'), ('Anne Bonny', 'PERSON'), ('Caribbean', 'LOC'), ('the 18th Century', 'DATE'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Oxford', 'PERSON'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Oxford', 'PRODUCT'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Universe', 'ORG'), ('Israeli', 'NORP'), ('November', 'DATE'), ('2020', 'DATE'), ('Sydney', 'GPE'), ('Yayoi Kusama', 'PERSON'), ('Kelly Grovier', 'PERSON'), ('the coming year', 'DATE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Skype', 'ORG'), ('Pep Guardiola', 'PERSON'), ('Manchester City', 'GPE'), ('Liverpool', 'PERSON'), ('11', 'CARDINAL'), ('2', 'CARDINAL'), ('Everton', 'PERSON'), ('Thousands', 'CARDINAL'), ('Mallacoota', 'GPE'), ('Victoria', 'PERSON'), ('Australia', 'GPE'), ('Some 12,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('the new decade', 'DATE'), ('Medinah', 'GPE'), ('Europe', 'LOC'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Solheim Cup', 'EVENT'), ('Rose', 'PERSON'), ('Rio', 'ORG'), ("Tiger's Masters", 'PERSON'), ('Carter', 'PERSON'), ('10 moments', 'TIME'), ('the decade', 'DATE'), ('another mega year', 'DATE'), ('Half a million', 'CARDINAL'), ('34th', 'ORDINAL'), ('annual', 'DATE'), ('London', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Baghdad', 'GPE'), ('more than four', 'CARDINAL'), ('2019', 'DATE'), ('Federica Valabrega', 'PERSON'), ('Orthodox', 'NORP'), ('Jewish', 'NORP'), ('New York', 'GPE'), ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'), ('Pope Francis', 'PERSON'), ("St Peter's", 'PERSON'), ("New Year's Eve", 'EVENT'), ('2019', 'DATE'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Chinese', 'NORP'), ('app', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Mark Noble', 'PERSON'), ("David Moyes'", 'PERSON'), ('West Ham', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Dan Rainsford', 'PERSON'), ('Sam Chatterley', 'PERSON'), ('Kim Jong-un', 'PERSON'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('15 January', 'DATE'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE'), ("Fallon Sherrock's", 'PERSON'), ('World Championship', 'EVENT'), ('New York', 'GPE'), ('Melbourne', 'GPE'), ('Barry Hearn', 'PERSON'), ('London', 'GPE'), ('Ugandan', 'NORP'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Africa', 'LOC'), ('this year', 'DATE'), ('Muslim', 'NORP'), ('Uttar', 'GPE'), ('WHO', 'ORG'), ('England', 'GPE'), ('Jofra Archer', 'PERSON'), ('second', 'ORDINAL'), ('South Africa', 'GPE'), ('Cape Town', 'GPE'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('2019', 'DATE'), ('West Virginia', 'GPE'), ('Two', 'CARDINAL'), ('20 minutes before midnight', 'TIME'), ("New Year's Eve", 'EVENT'), ('Cal-Mac', 'ORG'), ('Ferguson yard', 'ORG'), ('West Bromwich Albion and Leeds', 'ORG'), ('EFL', 'ORG'), ('Sweden', 'GPE'), ('Europe', 'LOC'), ('Tens of thousands', 'CARDINAL'), ('Hong Kong', 'GPE'), ('Pacific island', 'LOC'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Hereford', 'PERSON'), ('Worcestershire', 'PERSON'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Hereford', 'PERSON'), ('Worcester', 'PERSON'), ('The National Trust', 'ORG'), ('a good year', 'DATE'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('the Archbishop of Canterbury', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('today', 'DATE'), ('Luke Kemp', 'PERSON'), ('Zacatecas', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('British', 'NORP'), ("NHS England's", 'ORG'), ('the next decade', 'DATE'), ('Mark Lawrenson', 'PERSON'), ('Britain', 'GPE'), ('Got Talent', 'ORG'), ('Kojo Anim', 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Premier League', 'ORG'), ('2020', 'DATE'), ('Australia', 'GPE'), ('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('Japan', 'GPE'), ('Shuri Castle', 'PERSON'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('NHS', 'ORG'), ("Joe Biden's", 'PERSON'), ('Democratic', 'NORP'), ('Bernie Sanders', 'PERSON'), ('11 April 1970', 'DATE'), ('Moon', 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('the United States', 'GPE'), ('Seattle', 'GPE'), ('Washington', 'GPE'), ('21 January', 'DATE'), ('Eight million', 'CARDINAL'), ('Mumbai', 'GPE'), ('Southampton', 'ORG'), ('Premier League', 'ORG'), ('Photographer Jo Blackwell', 'PERSON'), ('52', 'CARDINAL'), ('115', 'CARDINAL'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('this week', 'DATE'), ('Boris Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('Singapore', 'GPE'), ('5', 'CARDINAL'), ('Chinese', 'NORP'), ('Asian Americans', 'NORP'), ('up to half', 'CARDINAL'), ('Earth', 'LOC'), ('ChopValue', 'ORG'), ('350,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('Vancouver', 'GPE'), ('every week', 'DATE'), ('Uefa', 'GPE'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Champions League', 'ORG'), ('Europa League', 'ORG'), ('season', 'DATE'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('BBC Radio Northampton', 'ORG'), ('102-year-old', 'DATE'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('communist', 'NORP'), ('NFL', 'ORG'), ('Spanish', 'NORP'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('a century ago', 'DATE'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Retailer', 'PERSON'), ('London', 'GPE'), ('Soyuz', 'PRODUCT'), ('Baikonur', 'GPE'), ('Kazakhstan', 'GPE'), ('Thirty', 'CARDINAL'), ('four-year-old', 'DATE'), ('the past 140 years', 'DATE'), ('Piobbico', 'PERSON'), ('Italy', 'GPE'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Cambridgeshire', 'GPE'), ('BBC Radio Cambridgeshire', 'ORG'), ('Jacinda Ardern', 'PERSON'), ('Korean', 'NORP'), ('Real Madrid', 'ORG'), ('Lorenzo Sanz', 'PERSON'), ('Georgia', 'GPE'), ('Tskaltubo', 'PERSON'), ('Soviet', 'NORP'), ('thousands', 'CARDINAL'), ('this week', 'DATE'), ('French', 'NORP'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('Friday', 'DATE'), ('Nicholas Barber', 'PERSON'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Greenland', 'ORG'), ('600 billion tonnes', 'QUANTITY'), ('the end of summer last year', 'DATE'), ("'9 to 5", 'DATE'), ('today', 'DATE'), ('thousands of years', 'DATE'), ('Australian', 'NORP'), ('Florida', 'GPE'), ('1985', 'DATE'), ('BBC News', 'ORG'), ('a day', 'DATE'), ('Australia', 'GPE'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Mark Easton', 'PERSON'), ('Bergamo', 'GPE'), ('Italy', 'GPE'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('Wales', 'GPE'), ('Millions', 'CARDINAL'), ('Indians', 'NORP'), ('the past two centuries', 'DATE'), ('8bn', 'MONEY'), ('6', 'MONEY'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Clare Thorp', 'ORG'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('last month', 'DATE'), ('New York', 'GPE'), ('Andrew Newey', 'PERSON'), ('Changpa', 'ORG'), ('80%', 'PERCENT'), ('up to £2,500', 'MONEY'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Serena Williams', 'PERSON'), ('Simone Biles', 'ORG'), ('more than two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Manchester United', 'ORG'), ('Gary Neville', 'PERSON'), ('more than £300bn', 'MONEY'), ('Nasa', 'ORG'), ('Denman Glacier', 'PERSON'), ('Earth', 'LOC'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('Stephen McDonell', 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('weeks', 'DATE'), ("South Africa's", 'GPE'), ('Cyril Ramaphosa', 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Canada', 'GPE'), ('New York', 'GPE'), ('California', 'GPE'), ('Washington', 'GPE'), ('Ischgl', 'GPE'), ('2020', 'DATE'), ('Olympic Games', 'EVENT'), ('a year', 'DATE'), ('International Olympic Committee', 'ORG'), ('Dick Pound', 'PERSON'), ('18-year-old', 'DATE'), ('England', 'GPE'), ('Stephen Fry', 'PERSON'), ('A third', 'CARDINAL'), ("New York's", 'GPE'), ('1,300', 'CARDINAL'), ('Spanish', 'NORP'), ('Instagram', 'PRODUCT'), ('daily', 'DATE'), ('5', 'CARDINAL'), ('Nick Green', 'PERSON'), ('the Social Distancing Festival', 'ORG'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('lurk', 'ORG'), ('Okanagan Lake', 'LOC'), ('Netflix', 'ORG'), ('Apple TV+', 'ORG'), ('Manchester United', 'ORG'), ('Marouane Fellaini', 'PERSON'), ('kindness', 'ORG'), ('Nigerian Victor Olaiya', 'PERSON'), ('last month', 'DATE'), ('Afrobeat', 'NORP'), ("McDonald's", 'ORG'), ('Nando', 'ORG'), ('Scotland', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('12', 'CARDINAL'), ('James Stephen', 'PERSON'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('billion-year-old', 'DATE'), ('Canadian', 'NORP'), ('Merkel', 'PERSON'), ('More than a billion', 'CARDINAL'), ('14-hours', 'DATE'), ('Kano', 'PERSON'), ('Nigeria', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Tokyo', 'GPE'), ('2020', 'DATE'), ('BBC Sport', 'ORG'), ('70s', 'DATE'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Boris Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('The International Olympic Committee', 'ORG'), ('Tokyo', 'GPE'), ('2020', 'DATE'), ('four weeks', 'DATE'), ('decades', 'DATE'), ('Amazon', 'ORG'), ('Ecuador', 'GPE'), ('Indonesia', 'GPE'), ('Each week', 'DATE'), ('Olympics', 'EVENT'), ('BBC Sport', 'ORG'), ('Emmerdale', 'ORG'), ('Lorraine', 'PERSON'), ('Asia', 'LOC'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('Monday', 'DATE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Michael Baum', 'PERSON'), ('French', 'NORP'), ('trans-Atlantic', 'LOC'), ('British', 'NORP'), ('Bali', 'GPE'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('25 years', 'DATE'), ("Alanis Morissette's", 'PERSON'), ('Jagged Little Pill', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('9/11', 'CARDINAL'), ('Indian', 'NORP'), ('More than 300,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('Jonathan Marcus', 'PERSON'), ('Germans', 'NORP'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('74', 'DATE'), ('Dani', 'PERSON'), ('Instagram', 'PRODUCT'), ('OECD', 'ORG'), ('Angel Gurría', 'ORG'), ('51-year-old', 'DATE'), ('Frankfurt', 'GPE'), ('30 years', 'DATE'), ('today', 'DATE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Japan', 'GPE'), ('Germany', 'GPE'), ('the early years', 'DATE'), ('the Gander Airport', 'FAC'), ('Newfoundland', 'GPE'), ('Canada', 'GPE'), ('Europe', 'LOC'), ('America', 'GPE'), ('7 June', 'DATE'), ('Australia', 'GPE'), ('One day', 'DATE'), ('Senate', 'ORG'), ('White House', 'ORG'), ('Republicans', 'NORP'), ('Mr Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Democrat', 'NORP'), ('Hollywood', 'GPE'), ('House', 'ORG'), ('Nancy Pelosi', 'PERSON'), ('Nicaragua', 'GPE'), ('Republican', 'NORP'), ('Romney', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Senate', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('annual', 'DATE'), ('Jonathan Turley', 'PERSON'), ('Georgia', 'GPE'), ('millions', 'CARDINAL'), ('Soviet', 'NORP'), ('Premier League Football', 'ORG'), ('BBC Sport', 'ORG'), ('Fianna Fáil', 'ORG'), ('Brexit', 'GPE'), ('mosque', 'FAC'), ('Indonesia', 'GPE'), ('last year', 'DATE'), ('FA Cup Football', 'EVENT'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Gwangju', 'PERSON'), ('Korean', 'NORP'), ('Carl De Keyzer', 'PERSON'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Democratic', 'NORP'), ('Wenjun Wang', 'PERSON'), ('House', 'ORG'), ('Flanker Lewis Ludlam', 'PERSON'), ('England', 'GPE'), ('Scotland', 'GPE'), ('Murrayfield', 'GPE'), ('Saturday', 'DATE'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Somi', 'GPE'), ('Nigeria', 'GPE'), ('this week', 'DATE'), ('Japan', 'GPE'), ('mid-century', 'DATE'), ('Los Angeles', 'GPE'), ('Ukrainian', 'NORP'), ('Uber Eats', 'ORG'), ('Transnistria', 'NORP'), ('Moldova', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Malawi', 'ORG'), ('Nasa', 'ORG'), ('Christina Koch', 'PERSON'), ('Cambridgeshire village', 'GPE'), ('Stilton', 'ORG'), ('Brexit', 'GPE'), ('99%', 'PERCENT'), ('today', 'DATE'), ('Finland', 'GPE'), ('the age of 65', 'DATE'), ('Tim', 'PERSON'), ('Kerala', 'GPE'), ('Jofra Archer', 'PERSON'), ('England', 'GPE'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Sri Lanka', 'GPE'), ('next month', 'DATE'), ('Indian', 'NORP'), ('Australia', 'GPE'), ('BBC Sport', 'ORG'), ('Nuro', 'ORG'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Nike', 'ORG'), ('World Athletics', 'ORG'), ('Winnie Mutembei', 'PERSON'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('Kenya', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Hildur Gudnadottir', 'PERSON'), ('The Australian Rugby League Commission', 'ORG'), ('year', 'DATE'), ('Georgia', 'GPE'), ('Tskaltubo', 'PERSON'), ('Soviet', 'NORP'), ('thousands', 'CARDINAL'), ('Manchester United Football', 'ORG'), ('BBC Sport', 'ORG'), ('About a quarter', 'DATE'), ('Wales', 'ORG'), ('A68', 'ORG'), ('AfD', 'ORG'), ('Thomas Kemmerich', 'PERSON'), ('Thuringia', 'GPE'), ('the London Palladium', 'ORG'), ('Wednesday', 'DATE'), ('Li Wenliang', 'PERSON'), ('Wuhan', 'GPE'), ('Boeing', 'ORG'), ('March 2019', 'DATE'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('346', 'CARDINAL'), ('About a third', 'CARDINAL'), ('FTSE', 'ORG'), ('100', 'CARDINAL'), ('Wednesday', 'DATE'), ('103', 'CARDINAL'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Kirk Douglas', 'PERSON'), ('100th', 'ORDINAL'), ('9 December', 'DATE'), ('Two', 'CARDINAL'), ('39', 'CARDINAL'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('2019', 'DATE'), ('Washington', 'GPE'), ('Boris Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('EU', 'ORG'), ('One', 'CARDINAL'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Damascus', 'GPE'), ('23', 'CARDINAL'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('CM Arvind Kejriwal', 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('PSNI', 'ORG'), ('Belfast', 'GPE'), ('31 January', 'DATE'), ('14 days', 'DATE'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Universe', 'ORG'), ('David Abel', 'PERSON'), ('the Diamond Princess', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Yokohama', 'GPE'), ('10', 'CARDINAL'), ('Joe Biden', 'PERSON'), ('Iowa', 'GPE'), ('Barcelona', 'ORG'), ('Eric Abidal', 'PERSON'), ('Lionel Messi', 'PERSON'), ('Microsoft', 'ORG'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('Hollywood', 'GPE'), ('Kirk Douglas', 'PERSON'), ('Bernie Sanders', 'PERSON'), ('second', 'ORDINAL'), ('Joe Biden', 'PERSON'), ('fourth', 'ORDINAL'), ('Europe', 'LOC'), ('Brighton', 'GPE'), ('London', 'GPE'), ('Jhon Jairo Velásquez', 'PERSON'), ('300', 'CARDINAL'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('the White House', 'ORG'), ('Gemma', 'ORG'), ('26', 'DATE'), ('three days', 'DATE'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Bristol', 'ORG'), ('BBC Radio', 'ORG'), ('Batley', 'PERSON'), ('Spen', 'PERSON'), ('Tracy Brabin', 'PERSON'), ('Shazia Ginai', 'PERSON'), ('decades', 'DATE'), ('1,500km', 'QUANTITY'), ('AfD', 'ORG'), ('German', 'NORP'), ('Jitterbug Boy', 'PERSON'), ('17,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('Indian', 'NORP'), ('Delhi', 'GPE'), ('the weekend', 'DATE'), ('Ray Kroc', 'PERSON'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Leicester', 'GPE'), ('BBC Radio Leicester', 'ORG'), ('the Tokyo Games', 'EVENT'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE'), ("South Africa's", 'GPE'), ("Derek Mackay's", 'PERSON'), ('Australia', 'GPE'), ('Darren Lehmann', 'PERSON'), ('Wednesday', 'DATE'), ('50th', 'ORDINAL'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Hollywood', 'GPE'), ('Donald Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Kalpana', 'ORG'), ('Facebook', 'ORG'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Bala Devi', 'PERSON'), ('Rangers FC', 'ORG'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Nintendo', 'ORG'), ('Japan', 'GPE'), ('Odion Ighalo', 'ORG'), ('Manchester United', 'ORG'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Chris Page', 'PERSON'), ('Saturday', 'DATE'), ('London', 'GPE'), ('year', 'DATE'), ('Bafta Film Awards', 'EVENT'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('BBC Radio Leeds', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('years', 'DATE'), ('more than 400', 'CARDINAL'), ('2001', 'DATE'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('European', 'NORP'), ('four weeks', 'DATE'), ('Southampton', 'GPE'), ('FA Cup', 'ORG'), ('Norwich City', 'GPE'), ('Pegasus Airlines', 'ORG'), ('Boeing', 'ORG'), ('737', 'PRODUCT'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Istanbul', 'GPE'), ('thousands', 'CARDINAL'), ('Hong Kong', 'GPE'), ('Cathay Pacific', 'ORG'), ('three weeks', 'DATE'), ('Vaan Island', 'GPE'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('Gulf of Mannar', 'ORG'), ('the Laccadive Sea', 'LOC'), ('Xbox', 'GPE'), ('Phil Spencer', 'PERSON'), ('Amazon', 'ORG'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('this week', 'DATE'), ('Iowa', 'GPE'), ('Shanghai', 'GPE'), ('Mike Lynch', 'PERSON'), ("BBC Culture's", 'ORG'), ('BP', 'ORG'), ('Bernard Looney', 'PERSON'), ('England', 'GPE'), ('Eddie Jones', 'PERSON'), ('scrum-half', 'DATE'), ('Ben Youngs', 'PERSON'), ('five', 'CARDINAL'), ('Scotland', 'GPE'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('34', 'CARDINAL'), ('Tom Werner', 'PERSON'), ("Jurgen Klopp's", 'PERSON'), ('this season', 'DATE'), ('millions', 'CARDINAL'), ("The Children's Laureate", 'ORG'), ('third', 'ORDINAL'), ('Spartacus', 'ORG'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Hollywood', 'GPE'), ('103', 'CARDINAL'), ('Premier League', 'ORG'), ('the summer', 'DATE'), ('Europe', 'LOC'), ('Greens', 'NORP'), ("People's Party", 'ORG'), ('Australia', 'GPE'), ('Marylène Lévesque', 'PERSON'), ('Zamira Hajiyeva', 'PERSON'), ('National Crime Agency', 'ORG'), ('Saline', 'GPE'), ('Michigan', 'GPE'), ('Wuhan', 'GPE'), ('hundreds', 'CARDINAL'), ('Corteva Agriscience', 'ORG'), ('Kirk Douglas', 'PERSON'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Hollywood', 'GPE'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Seoul', 'GPE'), ('Two thirds', 'CARDINAL'), ('American', 'NORP'), ('Richard Garriott', 'PERSON'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('Australian', 'NORP'), ('Li Wenliang', 'PERSON'), ('December', 'DATE'), ('eight-year-old', 'DATE'), ('Licypriya Kangujam', 'PERSON'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('£16m', 'MONEY'), ('Harrods', 'ORG'), ('Michael Douglas', 'PERSON'), ('Catherine Zeta-Jones', 'PERSON'), ('Canadians', 'NORP'), ('last week', 'DATE'), ('John Davies', 'PERSON'), ('the 1980s', 'DATE'), ('Argan', 'ORG'), ('Marie McCourt', 'PERSON'), ('Helen', 'PERSON'), ('the fourth financial quarter', 'DATE'), ('Thuringia', 'PERSON'), ('Germany', 'GPE'), ('Jenny Hill', 'PERSON'), ('Cynthia Erivo', 'PERSON'), ('Oscar', 'PERSON'), ('this year', 'DATE'), ('West Ham', 'GPE'), ('David Gold', 'PERSON'), ('500,000', 'MONEY'), ('Lamborghinis', 'PRODUCT'), ('WBC', 'ORG'), ('Deontay Wilder', 'PERSON'), ('NFL', 'ORG'), ('Odell Beckham Jr', 'PERSON'), ("Claudia Andujar's", 'PERSON'), ('Yanomami', 'NORP'), ('Acquittal', 'ORG'), ('California', 'GPE'), ('a decade', 'DATE'), ('Greg', 'PERSON'), ('Marie', 'PERSON'), ('House', 'ORG'), ('Rugby League', 'ORG'), ('BBC Sport', 'ORG'), ('eighth', 'ORDINAL'), ('Paula Jackson', 'PERSON'), ('800', 'CARDINAL'), ('Gaborone', 'GPE'), ('Botswana', 'GPE'), ('Yogi Adityanath', 'PERSON'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Australian', 'NORP'), ('Wuhan', 'GPE'), ('Christmas Island', 'LOC'), ("Anthony Joshua's", 'PERSON'), ('Tottenham Hotspur Stadium', 'FAC'), ('Eddie Hearn', 'PERSON'), ('Germany', 'GPE'), ('third', 'ORDINAL'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Bedfordshire', 'GPE'), ('Hertfordshire', 'PERSON'), ('Buckinghamshire', 'PERSON'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Three', 'CARDINAL'), ('two-week', 'DATE'), ('the US Senate', 'ORG'), ('Donald Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Robert Lewandowski', 'PERSON'), ('34th', 'ORDINAL'), ('35th', 'ORDINAL'), ('Bayern Munich', 'LOC'), ('Hoffenheim', 'NORP'), ('the German Cup quarter-finals', 'EVENT'), ('102', 'CARDINAL'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('90', 'CARDINAL'), ('Two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Chinese', 'NORP'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Australian', 'NORP'), ('the days', 'DATE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Donald Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Huoshenshan Hospital', 'PERSON'), ('about 1,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('French', 'NORP'), ('The Leeds University', 'ORG'), ('86', 'CARDINAL'), ('Hashem Abedi', 'ORG'), ('hundreds', 'CARDINAL'), ('May 2017', 'DATE'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE'), ("Donald Trump's", 'PERSON'), ('One', 'CARDINAL'), ('62', 'MONEY'), ('post-Brexit', 'ORG'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('more than a month', 'DATE'), ('Photographer Jo Blackwell', 'PERSON'), ('52', 'CARDINAL'), ('115', 'CARDINAL'), ('The French Open', 'EVENT'), ('September', 'DATE'), ('October', 'DATE'), ('one year', 'DATE'), ('2021', 'DATE'), ('Quarterback Tom Brady', 'PERSON'), ('the New England Patriots', 'ORG'), ('20-year', 'DATE'), ('six', 'CARDINAL'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('England', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('the next 15 days', 'DATE'), ('Americans', 'NORP'), ('more than 10', 'CARDINAL'), ('Woolworths', 'ORG'), ('elderly hour', 'TIME'), ('Five hundred years', 'DATE'), ('French', 'NORP'), ('Sydney', 'GPE'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('Morocco', 'GPE'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Aida Amoako', 'PERSON'), ('eleven', 'CARDINAL'), ('Chuck Berry’s', 'PERSON'), ('Gibson guitar', 'ORG'), ('John Lennon’s Steinway', 'PERSON'), ('Matt Colvin', 'PERSON'), ('Tennessee', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('17,700', 'CARDINAL'), ('Amazon', 'ORG'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('BBC Radio Northampton', 'ORG'), ('Uber', 'ORG'), ('Conor Madden', 'PERSON'), ('Hamlet', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('NFL', 'ORG'), ('Bible Museum', 'ORG'), ("The European Commission's", 'ORG'), ('Seattle', 'GPE'), ("Paul McCartney's", 'PERSON'), ('10,000', 'MONEY'), ('Tedros Adhanom', 'PERSON'), ('Over half a dozen', 'CARDINAL'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('more than 50', 'CARDINAL'), ("Indira Flack's", 'PERSON'), ('British', 'NORP'), ('30s', 'DATE'), ('Canadian', 'NORP'), ('more than 4,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('six', 'CARDINAL'), ('Idris Elba', 'PERSON'), ('daily', 'DATE'), ('Roberto Firmino', 'PERSON'), ('Andrew Newey', 'PERSON'), ('Changpa', 'ORG'), ('thousands', 'CARDINAL'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('Bernie Sanders', 'PERSON'), ('Michigan', 'GPE'), ('Democratic', 'NORP'), ('English', 'LANGUAGE'), ('International Olympic Committee', 'ORG'), ('Hayley Wickenheiser', 'PERSON'), ('the Tokyo Games', 'EVENT'), ('decades', 'DATE'), ('East Africa', 'GPE'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Canadian', 'NORP'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('Boris Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('Ohio', 'GPE'), ('Democratic', 'NORP'), ('American', 'NORP'), ('Europe', 'LOC'), ('Japan', 'GPE'), ('Canada', 'GPE'), ('Indian', 'NORP'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Donald Trump', 'PERSON'), ('pan-European', 'NORP'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('daily', 'DATE'), ('hundreds of thousands', 'CARDINAL'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('Olympics', 'EVENT'), ('BBC Sport', 'ORG'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('Apple', 'ORG'), ('30 days', 'DATE'), ('Americans', 'NORP'), ('treasury', 'ORG'), ('Hong Kong', 'GPE'), ('57', 'CARDINAL'), ('the past two weeks', 'DATE'), ('50', 'CARDINAL'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Joe Biden', 'PERSON'), ('Bernie Sanders', 'PERSON'), ('Democratic', 'NORP'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Britain', 'GPE'), ('around 2%', 'PERCENT'), ("Benjamin Netanyahu's", 'PERSON'), ('Adnan al-Zurfi', 'PERSON'), ('The International Commission on Non-Ionizing Radiation Protection', 'ORG'), ('this week', 'DATE'), ('Boris Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('Ireland', 'GPE'), ('this year', 'DATE'), ('Australian', 'NORP'), ('four', 'CARDINAL'), ('decades', 'DATE'), ('Amazon', 'ORG'), ('Ecuador', 'GPE'), ('James Stephen', 'PERSON'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('Americans', 'NORP'), ('40-year-old', 'DATE'), ('Spain', 'GPE'), ('Virgin Atlantic', 'GPE'), ('BA', 'GPE'), ('IAG', 'ORG'), ('Ryanair', 'ORG'), ('EasyJet', 'ORG'), ('Ellesmere Port', 'ORG'), ('Luton', 'GPE'), ("BBC Sport's", 'ORG'), ('Tom Fordyce', 'PERSON'), ('Katrina Lake', 'LOC'), ('Japan', 'GPE'), ('Five', 'CARDINAL'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('the Tokyo 2020 Olympic and Paralympic Games', 'ORG'), ('Euro 2020', 'LAW'), ('Venice', 'GPE'), ('Salah Abdeslam', 'PERSON'), ('2015', 'DATE'), ('20', 'CARDINAL'), ('Twenty years ago', 'DATE'), ('Uganda', 'GPE'), ('Japan', 'GPE'), ('the 2020 Tokyo Olympics', 'EVENT'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('the ninth Century', 'DATE'), ('Sweden', 'GPE'), ('European', 'NORP'), ("South Korea's", 'GPE'), ('Kang Kyung-wha', 'PERSON'), ("South Korea's", 'GPE'), ('Dow Jones', 'ORG'), ('12', 'CARDINAL'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('Europe', 'LOC'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Italy', 'GPE'), ('3D', 'CARDINAL'), ('30-day', 'DATE'), ('Cambridge', 'ORG'), ('Los Angeles', 'GPE'), ('Scottish', 'NORP'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Scotland', 'GPE'), ('Scotland', 'GPE'), ('Tens of millions', 'CARDINAL'), ('Americans', 'NORP'), ('30', 'CARDINAL'), ('Nicholas Barber', 'PERSON'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('50bn', 'MONEY'), ('Satoshi Uematsu', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Great Britain', 'GPE'), ('Wednesday', 'DATE'), ('the end of April', 'DATE'), ('British', 'NORP'), ('two weeks', 'DATE'), ('Texas', 'GPE'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Croatia', 'GPE'), ('Austria', 'GPE'), ('Trinidad', 'GPE'), ('Tobago', 'GPE'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('531', 'CARDINAL'), ('Israeli', 'NORP'), ('the Red Planet', 'LOC'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('Siberia', 'LOC'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('New Zealanders', 'NORP'), ('One', 'CARDINAL'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Watford', 'GPE'), ('Burnley', 'PERSON'), ('Ian Woan', 'PERSON'), ('six', 'CARDINAL'), ('Phil McNulty', 'PERSON'), ('10', 'CARDINAL'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Rapper Tekashi', 'PERSON'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('UAE', 'ORG'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Frederic Yonnet', 'PERSON'), ('London', 'GPE'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Treasury', 'ORG'), ('the Bank of England', 'ORG'), ('Afghan', 'NORP'), ('Europe', 'LOC'), ('Malakasa', 'GPE'), ('Delhi', 'GPE'), ('Twelve', 'CARDINAL'), ('Virunga National Park', 'FAC'), ('Congo', 'GPE'), ('last month', 'DATE'), ('this week', 'DATE'), ('the Red Planet', 'LOC'), ('app', 'ORG'), ('second', 'ORDINAL'), ('Japan', 'GPE'), ('Hokkaido', 'GPE'), ('Japan', 'GPE'), ('Santiago', 'GPE'), ('El Bosque', 'FAC'), ('Kevin Mayer', 'PERSON'), ('more than four million', 'CARDINAL'), ('100-year-old', 'DATE'), ('32', 'MONEY'), ('100', 'CARDINAL'), ('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Europe', 'LOC'), ('CCTV', 'ORG'), ('Ritz', 'ORG'), ('Barclay', 'ORG'), ('Laura Page', 'PERSON'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('Italy', 'GPE'), ('Flavia', 'PERSON'), ('José', 'ORG'), ('seven weeks ago', 'DATE'), ('five', 'CARDINAL'), ('Bundesliga', 'ORG'), ("next weekend's", 'DATE'), ("Hertha Berlin's", 'GPE'), ('Saturday', 'DATE'), ('3-0', 'DATE'), ('Neil Lennon', 'PERSON'), ('Celtic', 'NORP'), ('ninth', 'ORDINAL'), ('10th', 'ORDINAL'), ('Li Jingzhi', 'PERSON'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('Mao Yin', 'PERSON'), ('1988', 'DATE'), ('Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('National Cyber Security Centre', 'ORG'), ('Andrew Cuomo', 'PERSON'), ('England', 'GPE'), ('Gregory Tyree Boyce', 'PERSON'), ('Tyler', 'PERSON'), ('Bella', 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('2008', 'DATE'), ('Europe', 'LOC'), ('almost half', 'CARDINAL'), ('Tuesday', 'DATE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('UN', 'ORG'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Bristol', 'ORG'), ('BBC Radio', 'ORG'), ('Chelsea', 'ORG'), ('Callum Hudson-Odoi', 'PERSON'), ('Tuesday', 'DATE'), ('the early hours of', 'TIME'), ('app', 'ORG'), ('Scrabble app', 'PERSON'), ('hundreds', 'CARDINAL'), ('the night', 'TIME'), ('year', 'DATE'), ('Months', 'DATE'), ('thousands', 'CARDINAL'), ('SSE', 'ORG'), ('more than a millennium', 'DATE'), ('Burundi', 'GPE'), ('five years ago', 'DATE'), ("Michael Jordan's", 'PERSON'), ('1985', 'DATE'), ('a record $560,000', 'MONEY'), ('463,000', 'MONEY'), ('Ray McDermott', 'PERSON'), ('Welsh', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('State', 'ORG'), ('the last century', 'DATE'), ('the early days', 'DATE'), ('English', 'LANGUAGE'), ('Joe Bagley', 'PERSON'), ('Adam Becker', 'PERSON'), ('Melissa Hogenboom', 'PERSON'), ('Michael Marshall', 'PERSON'), ('Pomona Pictures', 'ORG'), ('Saudi Air Force', 'ORG'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Americans', 'NORP'), ('Florida', 'GPE'), ('Yemen', 'GPE'), ('Facebook', 'ORG'), ('about 100', 'CARDINAL'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('Jewish', 'NORP'), ('Six days', 'DATE'), ('the VE Day anniversary', 'EVENT'), ('Covid', 'ORG'), ('Bradford Royal Infirmary', 'ORG'), ('the next academic year', 'DATE'), ('Coronavirus', 'ORG'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Brussels', 'GPE'), ('Sophie Wilmès', 'PERSON'), ('30', 'CARDINAL'), ('Rusty Hutson Jr', 'PERSON'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Diversified Gas & Oil', 'ORG'), ('Amina', 'GPE'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Afghan', 'NORP'), ('24', 'CARDINAL'), ('last week', 'DATE'), ('The World Health Organization', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('the early days', 'DATE'), ('Firooza Omar', 'PERSON'), ('Afghan', 'NORP'), ('week', 'DATE'), ('Scott Morrison -', 'PERSON'), ('Ramadan', 'PERSON'), ('Broad Street', 'FAC'), ('Port Talbot', 'FAC'), ('Broadway', 'FAC'), ('New York', 'GPE'), ('Hollywood', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('the Premier League', 'ORG'), ('Pakistan', 'GPE'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('19', 'CARDINAL'), ('New York', 'GPE'), ('Beijing', 'GPE'), ('Panama', 'GPE'), ('days', 'DATE'), ('the day', 'DATE'), ('England', 'GPE'), ('Monday', 'DATE'), ('Jayaseelan', 'PERSON'), ('London', 'GPE'), ('Kambole Campbell', 'PERSON'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Formula 1', 'PERSON'), ('British', 'NORP'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('the night', 'TIME'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('Corteva Agriscience', 'ORG'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ("Manchester City's", 'GPE'), ('two-year', 'DATE'), ('European', 'NORP'), ('8 June', 'DATE'), ('the Court of Arbitration for Sport (Cas', 'ORG'), ('Thailand', 'GPE'), ('One', 'CARDINAL'), ('years', 'DATE'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Laura Foster', 'PERSON'), ('2012', 'DATE'), ('Nobel prize', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Svetlana Alexievich', 'PERSON'), ('hundreds', 'CARDINAL'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Australia', 'GPE'), ('110 million years ago', 'DATE'), ('70 million years', 'DATE'), ('Elon Musk', 'PERSON'), ('Tesla', 'ORDINAL'), ('1,000', 'MONEY'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('the Luckin Coffee', 'ORG'), ('Sunak', 'DATE'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('April', 'DATE'), ('The US Supreme Court', 'ORG'), ('1998', 'DATE'), ('Kenya', 'GPE'), ('Tanzania', 'GPE'), ('daily', 'DATE'), ('CO2', 'PERSON'), ('French', 'NORP'), ('seven', 'CARDINAL'), ('Rainbow Six', 'PERSON'), ('Cyril Ramaphosa', 'PERSON'), ('about $36,000', 'MONEY'), ('2017', 'DATE'), ('third', 'ORDINAL'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('more than four years', 'DATE'), ('2000', 'DATE'), ('Spike Lee’s', 'PERSON'), ('Canadian', 'NORP'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('UN', 'ORG'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('Denmark', 'GPE'), ('a month', 'DATE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Europe', 'LOC'), ('South East Asia', 'LOC'), ('three-month', 'DATE'), ('Chinese', 'NORP'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('more than £30bn', 'MONEY'), ('Klein', 'PERSON'), ('Europe', 'LOC'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Ramaphosa', 'PERSON'), ('One', 'CARDINAL'), ('Welsh Water', 'PERSON'), ('Canada', 'GPE'), ('Competition Bureau', 'ORG'), ('third', 'ORDINAL'), ('Australia', 'GPE'), ('Twenty-six', 'DATE'), ('35', 'CARDINAL'), ('EU', 'ORG'), ('this week', 'DATE'), ('Watford', 'ORG'), ('Troy Deeney', 'PERSON'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('the United States', 'GPE'), ('Swedish', 'NORP'), ("Joe Biden's", 'PERSON'), ('Democratic', 'NORP'), ('Bernie Sanders', 'PERSON'), ('Premier League', 'ORG'), ('the National Health Service', 'ORG'), ('Maeve Kennedy McKean', 'PERSON'), ('Chesapeake Bay', 'LOC'), ('Maryland', 'GPE'), ('last week', 'DATE'), ('More than 1,800', 'CARDINAL'), ('Tuesday', 'DATE'), ('John Prine', 'PERSON'), ('Italy', 'GPE'), ('Spain', 'GPE'), ('European', 'NORP'), ('2019', 'DATE'), ('Ashes Test', 'EVENT'), ('25 million', 'CARDINAL'), ('Dominic Raab', 'PERSON'), ('Boris Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('Zoom', 'PERSON'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('Boris Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('Europe', 'LOC'), ('1942', 'DATE'), ('Felice Benuzzi', 'ORG'), ('Mt Kenya', 'PERSON'), ("BBC Click's", 'ORG'), ('Chris Fox', 'PERSON'), ('Italy', 'GPE'), ('Spain', 'GPE'), ('EU', 'ORG'), ('Modernist', 'NORP'), ('20th-Century', 'DATE'), ('Clare Dowdy', 'PERSON'), ('the weekend', 'DATE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('first day', 'DATE'), ('Mauro Ferrari', 'PERSON'), ('EU', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('two weeks', 'DATE'), ('Hungry', 'ORG'), ('Mike Horn', 'PERSON'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('recent decades', 'DATE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('London', 'GPE'), ('Notting Hill Gate', 'FAC'), ('Monday night', 'TIME'), ('Navy', 'ORG'), ("BBC Click's", 'ORG'), ('Omar Mehtab', 'PERSON'), ('week', 'DATE'), ('3', 'CARDINAL'), ('Chrystal Ding', 'PERSON'), ('Rwanda', 'GPE'), ('Premier League', 'ORG'), ('1bn', 'ORDINAL'), ('FA', 'ORG'), ('English', 'NORP'), ('UN', 'ORG'), ('Saudi', 'NORP'), ('Houthi', 'ORG'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('10,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('Vermont', 'GPE'), ('Azul Rojas Marín', 'PERSON'), ('Peru', 'GPE'), ('this week', 'DATE'), ('A month', 'DATE'), ('Italy', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('Joe Biden', 'PERSON'), ('Democratic', 'NORP'), ('Donald Trump', 'PERSON'), ('British-African', 'NORP'), ('DontRush', 'PRODUCT'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('January', 'DATE'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('30%', 'PERCENT'), ('Rouhani', 'PERSON'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Chicagoans', 'NORP'), ('70%', 'PERCENT'), ('30%', 'PERCENT'), ('Indians', 'NORP'), ('Rwanda', 'GPE'), ('Paul Kagame', 'PERSON'), ('Turkmenistan', 'GPE'), ('Jeremy Vine', 'PERSON'), ('Chinese', 'NORP'), ('Rishi Sunak', 'PERSON'), ('750', 'MONEY'), ('Zoe', 'PERSON'), ('Tom', 'PERSON'), ('Wisconsin', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('fourth', 'ORDINAL'), ('White House', 'ORG'), ("Frank Gardner's", 'PERSON'), ('Japanese', 'NORP'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('the World Health Organization', 'ORG'), ('the Red Sea', 'LOC'), ('Israeli', 'NORP'), ('Linda Tripp', 'PERSON'), ("Bill Clinton's", 'PERSON'), ('White House', 'ORG'), ('Monica Lewinsky', 'PERSON'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('nearly 10', 'CARDINAL'), ('Sarin', 'ORG'), ('Latamina', 'PERSON'), ('March 2017', 'DATE'), ('Samsung', 'ORG'), ('2,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('Facebook', 'ORG'), ('Portal', 'ORG'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Geoff Chutter', 'PERSON'), ('Whitewater West', 'ORG'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Fergus Walsh', 'PERSON'), ('University College Hospital London', 'ORG'), ('5', 'CARDINAL'), ('24', 'CARDINAL'), ('one hour', 'TIME'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Wednesday', 'DATE'), ('Canadian', 'NORP'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('Cineworld', 'ORG'), ('almost 50%', 'PERCENT'), ('Carnival', 'ORG'), ('22%', 'PERCENT'), ('Wuhan', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('January', 'DATE'), ('Tedros Adhanom Ghebreyesus', 'PERSON'), ('the past 24 hours', 'TIME'), ('607', 'CARDINAL'), ('Keir Starmer', 'PERSON'), ('Jack Dorsey', 'PERSON'), ('28%', 'PERCENT'), ('US Democratic', 'NORP'), ("George Pell's", 'PERSON'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Larushka Ivan-Zadeh', 'PERSON'), ('hundreds of years', 'DATE'), ('Ottoman', 'NORP'), ('Turkish', 'NORP'), ('Boris Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('Dominic Raab', 'PERSON'), ('Rafael Correa', 'PERSON'), ('Belgium', 'GPE'), ('19', 'CARDINAL'), ('Belarus', 'GPE'), ("South Africa's", 'GPE'), ('Cape Town', 'GPE'), ('Arthur Brand', 'PERSON'), ('Picassos', 'ORG'), ('Van Goghs', 'PERSON'), ('Boris Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('938', 'CARDINAL'), ('daily', 'DATE'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('nearly 200 million', 'CARDINAL'), ('UN', 'ORG'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('about the third season', 'DATE'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Nasa', 'ORG'), ('Faiz Ilyas', 'PERSON'), ('24', 'DATE'), ('EU', 'ORG'), ('Poland', 'GPE'), ('Law', 'PERSON'), ('Justice Party', 'ORG'), ('Nigeria', 'GPE'), ('DW Fitness First', 'ORG'), ('Martin Long', 'PERSON'), ('monthly', 'DATE'), ('EU', 'ORG'), ('the Day', 'DATE'), ('Premier League', 'ORG'), ('Grammy', 'PERSON'), ('73', 'DATE'), ("George Pell's", 'PERSON'), ('Fiona Kolbinger', 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('One', 'CARDINAL'), ('Kenya', 'GPE'), ('Tuesday', 'DATE'), ('the age of 89', 'DATE'), ('1984', 'DATE'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Boris Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('16 hours', 'TIME'), ('EU', 'ORG'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('England', 'GPE'), ('Tottenham', 'GPE'), ('Chelsea', 'ORG'), ('West Ham', 'GPE'), ('Jimmy Greaves', 'PERSON'), ('Tom Brady', 'PERSON'), ('the start of last season', 'DATE'), ('last year', 'DATE'), ('New England Patriots', 'ORG'), ('EU', 'ORG'), ('16 hours', 'TIME'), ('Facebook', 'ORG'), ('Charlatans', 'NORP'), ('Amazon', 'ORG'), ('the end of the last ice age', 'DATE'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('London', 'GPE'), ('The World Trade Organization', 'ORG'), ('WTO', 'ORG'), ('between 13% and 32%', 'PERCENT'), ('this year', 'DATE'), ('Boris Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('morning', 'TIME'), ('Wednesday 8 April 2020', 'DATE'), ('Democratic', 'NORP'), ('Supreme Court', 'ORG'), ('Premier League', 'ORG'), ('Alan Shearer', 'PERSON'), ("McDonald's", 'ORG'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('many decades', 'DATE'), ('Eileen Gray', 'PERSON'), ('Wuhan', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('La Luz', 'ORG'), ('del Mundo', 'ORG'), ('German', 'NORP'), ('Germanwings', 'ORG'), ('more than 40', 'CARDINAL'), ('More than 2m', 'CARDINAL'), ('March', 'DATE'), ('FBI', 'ORG'), ('3', 'CARDINAL'), ('Jakarta', 'GPE'), ('Indonesian', 'NORP'), ("Real Madrid's", 'ORG'), ('10-20%', 'PERCENT'), ('thousands', 'CARDINAL'), ('Cuomo', 'PERSON'), ('Rikers', 'NORP'), ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'), ('Palestinian', 'NORP'), ('Four thousand years ago', 'DATE'), ('Harappan', 'PERSON'), ('modern-day', 'DATE'), ('Pakistan', 'GPE'), ('Ying Ying', 'PERSON'), ('Le Le', 'FAC'), ('Bernie Sanders', 'PERSON'), ('decades', 'DATE'), ('Democratic', 'NORP'), ('Dominic Raab', 'PERSON'), ('Dan Giannopoulos', 'PERSON'), ("Boris Johnson's", 'PERSON'), ('938', 'CARDINAL'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('a day', 'DATE'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Quibi', 'ORG'), ('10-minute', 'TIME'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('Coronavirus', 'ORG'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Jews', 'NORP'), ('Finnish', 'NORP'), ('Democrat', 'NORP'), ('Washington', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('Wednesday', 'DATE'), ('app', 'ORG'), ('WHO', 'ORG'), ('millions', 'CARDINAL'), ('Chinese', 'NORP'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('Congolese', 'NORP'), ('Brazzaville', 'GPE'), ('Kinshasa', 'GPE'), ('Three', 'CARDINAL'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Aston Villa', 'GPE'), ("Garth Crooks'", 'ORG'), ('the week', 'DATE'), ('290', 'CARDINAL'), ('2024', 'DATE'), ('Flightradar24', 'PERSON'), ('two days', 'DATE'), ('Donald Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Joe Biden', 'PERSON'), ('Britain', 'GPE'), ('Heather Watson', 'PERSON'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('Fiona Ferro', 'ORG'), ('Serbia', 'GPE'), ('Novak Djokovic', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('The New York Times', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('years', 'DATE'), ('the Soviet Union', 'GPE'), ('Louis Vuitton', 'PERSON'), ('Tiffany', 'ORG'), ('last November', 'DATE'), ('Tottenham', 'PERSON'), ('Eric Dier', 'PERSON'), ('French', 'NORP'), ('weeks', 'DATE'), ("Paul Hart's", 'PERSON'), ('Network Rail', 'ORG'), ('Ellis', 'PERSON'), ('New South Wales', 'GPE'), ('Australia', 'GPE'), ('Heather Watson', 'PERSON'), ('British', 'NORP'), ('Briton', 'GPE'), ('French', 'NORP'), ('Serena Williams', 'PERSON'), ('24th', 'DATE'), ('American', 'NORP'), ('Kristie Ahn', 'PERSON'), ('French', 'NORP'), ('Mick Schumacher', 'PERSON'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Ferrari', 'ORG'), ('Formula 1', 'PRODUCT'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('just hours', 'TIME'), ('Christmas', 'DATE'), ('20th-Century', 'DATE'), ('zero', 'CARDINAL'), ('2050', 'DATE'), ('London', 'GPE'), ('National Police Chiefs Council', 'ORG'), ('Tweed', 'PERSON'), ('England', 'GPE'), ('Scotland', 'GPE'), ('Tinkerbell', 'ORG'), ('Peter Pan', 'PERSON'), ('Wendy', 'PERSON'), ('About 200', 'CARDINAL'), ('Tottenham', 'PERSON'), ('Chelsea', 'ORG'), ('fourth', 'ORDINAL'), ('the Carabao Cup', 'EVENT'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Phil McNulty', 'PERSON'), ('Little Grey', 'PERSON'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('Iceland', 'GPE'), ('Dublin', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Chinese', 'NORP'), ('Dave Ramsden', 'PERSON'), ('19-year-old', 'DATE'), ('two weeks', 'DATE'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Manchester', 'LOC'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Tim Davie', 'PERSON'), ('Twitter', 'ORG'), ('Chris Wallace', 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Man Utd', 'PERSON'), ('James', 'PERSON'), ('Norwich', 'PERSON'), ('Artemisia Gentileschi', 'PERSON'), ('centuries', 'DATE'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('2025', 'DATE'), ('Food & Drink', 'ORG'), ('Americans', 'NORP'), ('today', 'DATE'), ('Oneida', 'PERSON'), ('19th Century', 'DATE'), ('Tory', 'PERSON'), ('Armenia', 'GPE'), ('SU-25', 'PRODUCT'), ('Armenian', 'NORP'), ('Turkey', 'GPE'), ('more than 1,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('daily', 'DATE'), ('Mason Mount', 'PERSON'), ('fifth', 'ORDINAL'), ('Tottenham', 'PERSON'), ('Chelsea', 'ORG'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('the Carabao Cup quarter-finals', 'EVENT'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Raj Kapoor', 'PERSON'), ('Dilip Kumar', 'PERSON'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Humberside', 'NORP'), ('BBC Radio Humberside', 'ORG'), ('Chinese', 'NORP'), ('Islamic', 'NORP'), ('90 seconds', 'TIME'), ('30 minutes', 'TIME'), ('Lake Jackson', 'GPE'), ('Texas', 'GPE'), ('BBC Breakfast', 'ORG'), ('David Attenborough', 'PERSON'), ('A Life on Our Planet', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('daily', 'DATE'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('7,143', 'CARDINAL'), ('71', 'CARDINAL'), ('Vatican', 'FAC'), ('Rome', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('the New York Times', 'ORG'), ('just $750', 'MONEY'), ('2016', 'DATE'), ('2017', 'DATE'), ('Scottish', 'NORP'), ('Dean Nicholson', 'PERSON'), ('British', 'NORP'), ('Boseman', 'PERSON'), ('21', 'CARDINAL'), ('2016', 'DATE'), ('the Great Barrier Reef', 'FAC'), ('Australia', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Biden', 'ORG'), ('Lorraine Tabone', 'PERSON'), ('Newham', 'PERSON'), ('five years', 'DATE'), ('More than 150', 'CARDINAL'), ('Bougainville', 'GPE'), ('Rio Tinto', 'ORG'), ('three year old', 'DATE'), ('overnight', 'TIME'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Grace Smith', 'PERSON'), ('Sophia Smith-Galer', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('app', 'ORG'), ('Novak Djokovic', 'PERSON'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('the French Open', 'EVENT'), ('Sunday', 'DATE'), ('South Korean', 'NORP'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('the Lake District', 'LOC'), ('four-metre', 'QUANTITY'), ('13', 'CARDINAL'), ('the 1920s', 'DATE'), ('Italy', 'GPE'), ('Apulia', 'GPE'), ('French', 'NORP'), ('second', 'ORDINAL'), ('Cameron Norrie', 'PERSON'), ('Liam Broady', 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('the Château de Brézé', 'EVENT'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('Manchester United', 'ORG'), ('Jadon Sancho', 'ORG'), ('Pep Guardiola', 'PERSON'), ('Manchester City', 'GPE'), ('One', 'CARDINAL'), ('five', 'CARDINAL'), ('Jolyon Palmer', 'PERSON'), ('five', 'CARDINAL'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('EU', 'ORG'), ('84', 'CARDINAL'), ('Quim Torra', 'PERSON'), ('Armenia', 'GPE'), ('Azerbaijan', 'GPE'), ('Nagorno-Karabakh', 'LOC'), ('Jurgen Klopp', 'PERSON'), ('Manchester City', 'GPE'), ('Ruben Dias', 'PERSON'), ('Benfica', 'GPE'), ('six-year', 'DATE'), ('about £65', 'MONEY'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('Armenia', 'GPE'), ('Azerbaijan', 'GPE'), ('Liverpool', 'GPE'), ('Arsenal', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Chris Gorman', 'PERSON'), ('England', 'GPE'), ('Spain', 'GPE'), ('Rafael Nadal', 'PERSON'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Dominic Thiem', 'LOC'), ('French', 'NORP'), ('second', 'ORDINAL'), ('Daniil Medvedev', 'PERSON'), ('More than 30', 'CARDINAL'), ('naturalist', 'ORG'), ('UN', 'ORG'), ('Thousands', 'CARDINAL'), ('Australians', 'NORP'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('UN', 'ORG'), ('António Guterres', 'PERSON'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Antikythera', 'PERSON'), ('Sahara', 'LOC'), ('Mount Etna', 'LOC'), ('Canadian', 'NORP'), ('Joe Biden', 'PERSON'), ('nearly $288,000', 'MONEY'), ('224,000', 'MONEY'), ('last year', 'DATE'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('app', 'ORG'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Emmanuel "Onry" Henreid', 'PERSON'), ('Heather Watson', 'PERSON'), ('British', 'NORP'), ('French', 'NORP'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('Fiona Ferro', 'ORG'), ('Thirty years ago', 'DATE'), ('Heil Honey', 'PERSON'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Dutch', 'NORP'), ('the White House', 'FAC'), ("the Red Planet's", 'LOC'), ('Aston Villa', 'GPE'), ('Premier League', 'ORG'), ('Fulham', 'GPE'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Edinburgh', 'GPE'), ('Fife', 'GPE'), ('East Scotland', 'GPE'), ('BBC Radio', 'ORG'), ('Scotland', 'GPE'), ('Arctic', 'LOC'), ('Ohio', 'GPE'), ('Milan', 'GPE'), ('Week', 'DATE'), ('Boris Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('millions', 'CARDINAL'), ('Flash', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Facebook', 'ORG'), ('December', 'DATE'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('the ninth Century', 'DATE'), ('Sweden', 'GPE'), ('Czech', 'NORP'), ('second', 'ORDINAL'), ('Karolina', 'GPE'), ('Mayar Sherif', 'PERSON'), ('French', 'NORP'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Highlands', 'GPE'), ('Islands', 'LOC'), ('BBC Radio', 'ORG'), ('Scotland', 'GPE'), ('Novak Djokovic', 'PERSON'), ('French', 'NORP'), ('Sweden', 'GPE'), ('Mikael Ymer', 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Paris', 'GPE'), ('Aaron Sorkin', 'PERSON'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Will Gompertz', 'PERSON'), ('Kangana Ranaut', 'ORG'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Sheikh Sabah', 'ORG'), ('Gulf', 'LOC'), ('2006', 'DATE'), ('decades', 'DATE'), ('almost 200 years', 'DATE'), ('the United States', 'GPE'), ('America', 'GPE'), ('64%', 'PERCENT'), ('Deveselu', 'GPE'), ('American', 'NORP'), ("Jim Grover's", 'PERSON'), ('Clapham Common', 'PERSON'), ('Belarus', 'GPE'), ('tens of thousands', 'CARDINAL'), ('Alexander Lukashenko', 'PERSON'), ('Germany', 'GPE'), ('baker', 'PERSON'), ('around 50%', 'PERCENT'), ('1942', 'DATE'), ('Indian', 'NORP'), ('Himalayas', 'ORG'), ('Kansas City Chiefs', 'ORG'), ('Patrick Mahomes', 'ORG'), ('34', 'CARDINAL'), ('Baltimore', 'GPE'), ('week', 'DATE'), ('Theresa', 'ORG'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Sri Lanka', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Huawei', 'ORG'), ('Monday', 'DATE'), ('2012', 'DATE'), ('summer', 'DATE'), ('2020', 'DATE'), ('Ice Hockey', 'PERSON'), ('BBC Sport', 'ORG'), ('The commerce department', 'ORG'), ('Chinese', 'NORP'), ('Almost 200', 'CARDINAL'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('March', 'DATE'), ('the UN General Assembly', 'ORG'), ("Svetlana Alexievich's", 'PERSON'), ('Germany', 'GPE'), ('Belarus', 'GPE'), ('the Stanley Cup', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('2004', 'DATE'), ('4', 'CARDINAL'), ('Dallas', 'GPE'), ('Loyal', 'ORG'), ('Álvaro', 'ORG'), ('Colombians', 'NORP'), ('Nedum Onuoha', 'PERSON'), ('the Jacob Blake', 'LOC'), ('BBC Health', 'ORG'), ('Laura Foster', 'PERSON'), ('Lionel Messi', 'PERSON'), ('Pep Guardiola', 'PERSON'), ('Serge Reguilon', 'PERSON'), ('Chelsea', 'ORG'), ('Kai Havertz', 'NORP'), ('Ota Benga', 'PERSON'), ('DR Congo', 'ORG'), ('1904', 'DATE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Donald Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Americans', 'NORP'), ('Joe Biden', 'PERSON'), ('Franja Bidovec', 'ORG'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('20', 'CARDINAL'), ('World War Two', 'EVENT'), ('Slovenia', 'GPE'), ('Americans', 'NORP'), ('Wakayama', 'GPE'), ('Japan', 'GPE'), ('Unesco', 'ORG'), ('Valtteri Bottas', 'ORG'), ('Lewis Hamilton', 'PERSON'), ('Mercedes', 'FAC'), ('one-two', 'CARDINAL'), ("Red Bull's", 'ORG'), ('Max Verstappen', 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('the Belgian Grand Prix', 'EVENT'), ('Geraint Thomas', 'PERSON'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('the Republican Party', 'ORG'), ('the Party of Trump', 'ORG'), ('Louise Michel', 'PERSON'), ('Mediterranean', 'LOC'), ('Arsenal', 'ORG'), ('the Community Shield', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Wembley Stadium', 'FAC'), ('China Inc', 'ORG'), ('Joe Biden', 'PERSON'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Jerome Powell', 'PERSON'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Nearly 1,000 years ago', 'DATE'), ('French', 'NORP'), ('Intelligence', 'ORG'), ('the White House', 'FAC'), ('England', 'GPE'), ('Millie Bright', 'PERSON'), ('Chelsea', 'ORG'), ('Manchester City', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ("Women's Community Shield", 'EVENT'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('a second straight day', 'DATE'), ('Jacob Blake', 'PERSON'), ('Georgia', 'GPE'), ('400ft', 'QUANTITY'), ('122m', 'QUANTITY'), ('20-minute', 'TIME'), ('Lewis Hamilton', 'PERSON'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('the Belgium GP', 'FAC'), ('Barack Obama', 'PERSON'), ('Billie Eilish', 'NORP'), ('2012', 'DATE'), ('Craig Hodges', 'PERSON'), ('NBA', 'ORG'), ('1991', 'DATE'), ('2020', 'DATE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Kennedy', 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('Spain', 'GPE'), ('Germany', 'GPE'), ('Eoin Morgan', 'PERSON'), ('England', 'GPE'), ("next year's", 'DATE'), ('World T20', 'ORG'), ('Pakistan', 'GPE'), ('Friday', 'DATE'), ('Martin Luther King', 'PERSON'), ('Malcolm X', 'PERSON'), ('Kwame Nkrumah', 'ORG'), ('week', 'DATE'), ('four', 'CARDINAL'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Shinzo Abe', 'PERSON'), ('England', 'GPE'), ('Tom Banton', 'PERSON'), ('71', 'CARDINAL'), ('42', 'CARDINAL'), ('Pakistan', 'GPE'), ('Cricket South Africa', 'ORG'), ('Thabang Moroe', 'PERSON'), ('Eileen Wood', 'PERSON'), ('8ft', 'ORDINAL'), ('Jamie Lynn Spears', 'PERSON'), ('Britney', 'PERSON'), ('California', 'GPE'), ('Neuralink', 'ORG'), ('the White House', 'ORG'), ('Sky Sports', 'ORG'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Soccer', 'GPE'), ('Saturday', 'DATE'), ('Perth Zoo', 'ORG'), ('Australia', 'GPE'), ('Pierre', 'PERSON'), ('Amnesty International', 'ORG'), ('Hindu', 'NORP'), ('Muslims', 'NORP'), ("Manchester United's", 'ORG'), ('Harry Maguire', 'PERSON'), ('Greek', 'NORP'), ('last week', 'DATE'), ('Sydney', 'GPE'), ('Manchester City', 'GPE'), ('Riyad Mahrez', 'PERSON'), ('Bernardo Silva', 'PERSON'), ('Gabriel Jesus', 'PERSON'), ('Lionel Messi', 'ORG'), ('this summer', 'DATE'), ('four', 'CARDINAL'), ('Donald Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Republican', 'NORP'), ('November', 'DATE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('November', 'DATE'), ('PM Shinzo Abe', 'PERSON'), ('Republicans', 'NORP'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('UAE', 'ORG'), ('26', 'CARDINAL'), ('Libya', 'GPE'), ('Tripoli', 'GPE'), ('Siberia', 'LOC'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Cumbria', 'GPE'), ('BBC Radio Cumbria', 'ORG'), ('Epic', 'PERSON'), ('Apple', 'ORG'), ('Ivanka Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Japan', 'GPE'), ('this weekend', 'DATE'), ('53', 'CARDINAL'), ('Greater Andamanese', 'NORP'), ('10', 'CARDINAL'), ('Japan', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Walmart', 'ORG'), ('Chinese', 'NORP'), ('app', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Arsenal', 'ORG'), ('Mikel Arteta', 'PERSON'), ('Liverpool', 'GPE'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Bristol', 'ORG'), ('BBC Radio', 'ORG'), ('PSG', 'ORG'), ('Messi', 'PERSON'), ('Manchester City', 'GPE'), ('Chelsea', 'PERSON'), ('Barcelona', 'GPE'), ('Wijnaldum', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('70 minutes', 'TIME'), ('second', 'ORDINAL'), ('This month', 'DATE'), ('Mulan', 'ORG'), ('Gloria', 'GPE'), ('Donald Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Dame Vera Lynn', 'PERSON'), ('week', 'DATE'), ('Last Night of the Proms', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Harry-Wheeler', 'PERSON'), ('East Anglia', 'LOC'), ("Storm Francis's", 'ORG'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('Two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Frans Hals', 'PERSON'), ('Guangdong', 'GPE'), ('Sunday', 'DATE'), ('Hong Kong', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Dutch', 'NORP'), ('Taiwan', 'GPE'), ('Argentina', 'GPE'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('Covid', 'NORP'), ('BBC Radio', 'ORG'), ('Live Sports Extra', 'ORG'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('second', 'ORDINAL'), ('the Belgian Grand Prix', 'EVENT'), ("New Zealand's", 'GPE'), ('the fourth day in a row', 'DATE'), ('Jurgen Klopp', 'FAC'), ('Lionel Messi', 'ORG'), ('Argentine', 'NORP'), ("Red Bull's", 'ORG'), ('Max Verstappen', 'PERSON'), ('second', 'ORDINAL'), ('the Belgian Grand Prix', 'FAC'), ("Daniel Ricciardo's", 'PERSON'), ('Renault', 'ORG'), ('Mercedes', 'ORG'), ('35-year-old', 'DATE'), ('the White House', 'FAC'), ('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('Chelsea', 'ORG'), ('one-year', 'DATE'), ('Two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Wisconsin', 'GPE'), ('Indonesia', 'GPE'), ('Donald Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Republican', 'NORP'), ('3', 'CARDINAL'), ('November', 'PRODUCT'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('26-year-old', 'DATE'), ('five', 'CARDINAL'), ('Tom Banton', 'PERSON'), ('71', 'CARDINAL'), ('42', 'CARDINAL'), ('England', 'GPE'), ('Pakistan', 'GPE'), ('Rhea Chakraborty', 'PERSON'), ('Bollywood', 'GPE'), ('Manchester United', 'ORG'), ('Paul Pogba', 'PERSON'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('Didier Deschamps', 'PERSON'), ('Yaser Abdel Said', 'PERSON'), ('12 years', 'DATE'), ("the New Year's Day", 'EVENT'), ('Texas', 'GPE'), ('Hate Suzie', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Billie Piper', 'PERSON'), ('Secret Diary', 'PERSON'), ('Lucy Prebble', 'PERSON'), ('the Bletchley Park Trust', 'ORG'), ('geese', 'NORP'), ('jellyfish', 'NORP'), ('Japan', 'GPE'), ('Shinzo Abe', 'PERSON'), ('Ronan Hughes', 'PERSON'), ('39 migrants', 'QUANTITY'), ('Essex', 'GPE'), ('Bryce Hall', 'ORG'), ('Blake Gray', 'PERSON'), ('Los Angeles', 'GPE'), ('Hurricane Laura', 'ORG'), ('midnight', 'TIME'), ('05:00 GMT', 'TIME'), ('Cameron', 'GPE'), ('Louisiana', 'GPE'), ('Blake', 'PERSON'), ('Wisconsin', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Dutch', 'NORP'), ('four to five years', 'DATE'), ('recent years', 'DATE'), ('Two', 'CARDINAL'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('a third night', 'TIME'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Kenosha', 'GPE'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Australia', 'GPE'), ('Aaron Mooy', 'PERSON'), ('Shanghai', 'GPE'), ('Brighton', 'GPE'), ('Five', 'CARDINAL'), ('US', 'GPE'), ("Jacob Blake's", 'PERSON'), ('Corteva Agriscience', 'ORG'), ('Britain', 'GPE'), ('Andy Murray', 'PERSON'), ('Japan', 'GPE'), ('Yoshihito Nishioka', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Johanna Konta', 'PERSON'), ('Heather Watson', 'PERSON'), ('British', 'NORP'), ('2019', 'DATE'), ('Federica Valabrega', 'PERSON'), ('Orthodox', 'NORP'), ('Jewish', 'NORP'), ('New York', 'GPE'), ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'), ('Two', 'CARDINAL'), ('13', 'CARDINAL'), ('Indian', 'NORP'), ('the United Arab Emirates', 'GPE'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Edinburgh', 'GPE'), ('Fife', 'GPE'), ('East Scotland', 'GPE'), ('BBC Radio', 'ORG'), ('Scotland', 'GPE'), ('four-year-old', 'DATE'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('a night', 'TIME'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Suffolk', 'GPE'), ('BBC Radio Suffolk', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Republican', 'NORP'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Republicans', 'NORP'), ('2020', 'DATE'), ('Some 50,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('DC', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('National Mall', 'FAC'), ('EU', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Europe', 'LOC'), ('Japanese', 'NORP'), ('3,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('100 years ago', 'DATE'), ('American', 'NORP'), ('the past seven days', 'DATE'), ('NFL', 'ORG'), ('Baltimore', 'GPE'), ('the United States', 'GPE'), ("Northern Ireland's", 'GPE'), ('Rory McIlroy', 'GPE'), ('England', 'GPE'), ('Matthew Fitzpatrick', 'PERSON'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Hideki Matsuyama', 'PERSON'), ('BMW', 'ORG'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Japan', 'GPE'), ('Japanese', 'NORP'), ('Shinzo Abe', 'PERSON'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Maine', 'GPE'), ('Blake', 'PERSON'), ('Kyle Rittenhouse', 'PERSON'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Kenosha', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Daisy Dove Bloom', 'PERSON'), ('Four', 'CARDINAL'), ('year', 'DATE'), ('march', 'DATE'), ("George Floyd's", 'PERSON'), ('John Bel Edwards', 'PERSON'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Belarus', 'GPE'), ('Kevin Mayer', 'PERSON'), ('two months', 'DATE'), ('app', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('NBA', 'ORG'), ('a third straight day', 'DATE'), ('Saturday', 'DATE'), ('daily', 'DATE'), ('Jordan Mossom', 'PERSON'), ('Duchenne', 'PERSON'), ('George Floyd', 'PERSON'), ('1963', 'DATE'), ('March', 'DATE'), ('Washington', 'GPE'), ('Pakistan', 'GPE'), ('Karachi', 'PERSON'), ('Prince William', 'PERSON'), ('Prince Harry', 'PERSON'), ('Kensington Palace', 'FAC'), ('Yuri Ganus', 'PERSON'), ('zero', 'CARDINAL'), ('Gymnastics', 'ORG'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('months', 'DATE'), ('only two', 'CARDINAL'), ('November', 'DATE'), ('more than a year', 'DATE'), ('Greece', 'GPE'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Tom Moore', 'PERSON'), ('more than £12m', 'MONEY'), ('NHS', 'ORG'), ('27 May', 'DATE'), ('Wuhan', 'GPE'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('Yasuyoshi Chiba', 'PERSON'), ('Australia', 'GPE'), ('Earth', 'LOC'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Japanese', 'NORP'), ('Fifty years', 'DATE'), ('Andy Murray', 'PERSON'), ('Novak Djokovic', 'PERSON'), ('Instagram Live', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Apocalyptic', 'ORG'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('25 million', 'CARDINAL'), ('the Red Sea', 'LOC'), ('the past seven days', 'DATE'), ('BBC News', 'ORG'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('15,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Italy', 'GPE'), ('America', 'GPE'), ('349bn', 'MONEY'), ('Sahar Tabar', 'ORG'), ('Angelina Jolie', 'PERSON'), ('Guayaquil', 'ORG'), ('Latin America', 'LOC'), ('Germany', 'GPE'), ('Jennifer Keishin Armstrong', 'PERSON'), ('Japanese', 'NORP'), ('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('Britons', 'ORG'), ('the past 100 years', 'DATE'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('America', 'GPE'), ('2013', 'DATE'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('orange juice', 'ORG'), ('zinc lozenges', 'PERSON'), ('New York', 'GPE'), ('West Bengal', 'GPE'), ('Shiva', 'PERSON'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ("BBC Sport's", 'ORG'), ('weekly', 'DATE'), ('Brighton', 'ORG'), ('Tony Bloom', 'PERSON'), ('the Premier League', 'ORG'), ('Guayaquil', 'GPE'), ('nearly 6,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('two-week', 'DATE'), ('South Dakota', 'GPE'), ('Olympics', 'EVENT'), ('BBC Sport', 'ORG'), ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'), ('more than a million', 'CARDINAL'), ('One', 'CARDINAL'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Four', 'CARDINAL'), ('the Tokyo Olympics', 'EVENT'), ('99-year-old', 'DATE'), ('Tom Moore', 'PERSON'), ('West End', 'GPE'), ('Michael Ball', 'PERSON'), ('The World Health Organization', 'ORG'), ('Donald Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Europe', 'LOC'), ('over €20 billion', 'MONEY'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('WHO', 'ORG'), ('two million', 'CARDINAL'), ('Brewgooder', 'ORG'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('The Golden State', 'FAC'), ('about 100', 'CARDINAL'), ("last year's", 'DATE'), ('Covid-19', 'ORG'), ('Kristalina Georgieva', 'PERSON'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Premier League', 'ORG'), ('21', 'DATE'), ('the start of the season', 'DATE'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('Thomas Thabane', 'PERSON'), ('2017', 'DATE'), ('New Jersey', 'GPE'), ('last week', 'DATE'), ('Bangladesh', 'GPE'), ('Yanira Soriano', 'PERSON'), ('36', 'DATE'), ('week', 'DATE'), ('BCG jabs', 'PERSON'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('99-year-old', 'DATE'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Prince William', 'PERSON'), ('24 hours', 'TIME'), ('NHS Providers', 'ORG'), ('Rory Cellan-Jones', 'PERSON'), ('Lady Gaga', 'PERSON'), ('more than 100', 'CARDINAL'), ('The Premier League', 'ORG'), ('England', 'GPE'), ('Ian Wright', 'PERSON'), ('Europe', 'LOC'), ('Two', 'CARDINAL'), ('164', 'CARDINAL'), ('the past two decades', 'DATE'), ('three weeks', 'DATE'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('WHO', 'ORG'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Central Park', 'LOC'), ('New Yorkers', 'NORP'), ('Vitamin D', 'PERSON'), ('four', 'CARDINAL'), ('seconds', 'TIME'), ('400ml', 'FAC'), ('half', 'CARDINAL'), ('half', 'CARDINAL'), ('Melissa Hogenboom', 'PERSON'), ('this week', 'DATE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Donald Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Africa Eye', 'ORG'), ('the chaotic final months', 'DATE'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Boris Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('Tokyo', 'GPE'), ('2020', 'DATE'), ('next year', 'DATE'), ('Netherlands', 'GPE'), ('May', 'DATE'), ('decades', 'DATE'), ('Amazon', 'ORG'), ('Ecuador', 'GPE'), ('Lady Gaga', 'PERSON'), ('Billie Eilish', 'PERSON'), ('Taylor Swift', 'PERSON'), ('Paul McCartney', 'PERSON'), ('the Rolling Stones', 'ORG'), ('up to 30%', 'PERCENT'), ('the middle of the day', 'DATE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Bill Beaumont', 'PERSON'), ('Ali Sanders', 'PERSON'), ('more than 500', 'CARDINAL'), ('40-day', 'DATE'), ('Premier League', 'ORG'), ('Friday', 'DATE'), ('Spain', 'GPE'), ('Ethiopia', 'GPE'), ('Eritrea', 'GPE'), ('Barcelona', 'GPE'), ('Neymar', 'GPE'), ('Man Utd', 'PERSON'), ('Sao Paulo', 'GPE'), ('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('this week', 'DATE'), ('over 100', 'CARDINAL'), ('Devin Haney', 'PERSON'), ('Japan', 'GPE'), ('100%', 'PERCENT'), ('UN', 'ORG'), ('300,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('Africa', 'LOC'), ('millions', 'CARDINAL'), ('Brussels', 'GPE'), ('Tom Moore', 'PERSON'), ('millions', 'CARDINAL'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Bedfordshire', 'GPE'), ('Hertfordshire', 'PERSON'), ('Buckinghamshire', 'PERSON'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Millions', 'CARDINAL'), ("Jemima Yong's", 'PERSON'), ('London', 'GPE'), ('more than 500 years', 'DATE'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('25-year-old', 'DATE'), ('Georgia', 'GPE'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('Grant Shapps', 'PERSON'), ('Nissan', 'ORG'), ('Tokyo', 'GPE'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE'), ('Charts', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Red Square', 'FAC'), ('Belarus', 'GPE'), ('75th', 'ORDINAL'), ('VE Day', 'EVENT'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('Grant Shapps', 'PERSON'), ('9', 'CARDINAL'), ('World War Two', 'EVENT'), ('five', 'CARDINAL'), ('Fifa', 'ORG'), ('the end of May', 'DATE'), ('Paraguay', 'ORG'), ('South America', 'LOC'), ('Lake Victoria', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('649', 'CARDINAL'), ('30,076', 'CARDINAL'), ('Queen', 'PERSON'), ('75th', 'ORDINAL'), ('VE Day', 'EVENT'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('Two', 'CARDINAL'), ('AI', 'GPE'), ('Nvidia RTX Voice', 'ORG'), ('14%', 'PERCENT'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('years', 'DATE'), ('Texas', 'GPE'), ('25%', 'PERCENT'), ('Donald Trump', 'PERSON'), ('months', 'DATE'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('Spain', 'GPE'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('the past seven days', 'DATE'), ('one day', 'DATE'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Wanda Cooper', 'PERSON'), ('Ahmaud Arbery', 'ORG'), ('Belarus', 'ORG'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('VE Day', 'DATE'), ('Britain', 'GPE'), ('Germany', 'GPE'), ('1945', 'DATE'), ('Paul Fronczak', 'PERSON'), ('2019', 'DATE'), ('Sintra', 'ORG'), ('Quinta da Regaleira', 'PERSON'), ('Portugal', 'GPE'), ('Knights Templar', 'PERSON'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('Manchester', 'LOC'), ('Friday', 'DATE'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('years', 'DATE'), ('WHO', 'ORG'), ('Siegfried Fischbacher', 'PERSON'), ('Las Vegas', 'GPE'), ('World War Two', 'EVENT'), ('Nazi', 'NORP'), ('Netherlands', 'GPE'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('South Korea', 'GPE'), ('Renault', 'ORG'), ('Daniel Ricciardo', 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('the season', 'DATE'), ('Calais', 'GPE'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Hampshire', 'GPE'), ('the Isle of Wight:', 'GPE'), ('BBC Radio Solent', 'ORG'), ('the Flower Moon', 'LOC'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('this year', 'DATE'), ('Allan Little', 'PERSON'), ('VE Day', 'DATE'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Britain', 'GPE'), ('Two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Norfolk Island', 'GPE'), ('Seventy-five years', 'DATE'), ('Europe', 'LOC'), ('Thousands', 'CARDINAL'), ('PM Janez Jansa', 'PERSON'), ('this week', 'DATE'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('Bank of England', 'ORG'), ('Austria', 'GPE'), ('14 days', 'DATE'), ('190', 'MONEY'), ("last year's", 'DATE'), ('Red Square', 'FAC'), ('Elvis', 'ORG'), ('87', 'CARDINAL'), ('300 years', 'DATE'), ('Scotland', 'GPE'), ('England', 'GPE'), ('Ignaz Semmelweis', 'PERSON'), ('the 19th Century', 'DATE'), ('John Lewis', 'ORG'), ("Tutti Frutti's", 'PERSON'), ('Ray', 'PERSON'), ('Rinkoffs', 'ORG'), ('Millions', 'CARDINAL'), ('One', 'CARDINAL'), ('Earth', 'LOC'), ('1957', 'DATE'), ('East Asia', 'LOC'), ('a million', 'CARDINAL'), ('Elvis', 'ORG'), ('87', 'CARDINAL'), ('Watford', 'ORG'), ('third', 'ORDINAL'), ('Premier League', 'ORG'), ('One', 'CARDINAL'), ('from decades ago', 'DATE'), ('Ramayan', 'PERSON'), ('Shaktimaan', 'GPE'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('the 1930s', 'DATE'), ('Chelsea', 'ORG'), ('Chilwell', 'ORG'), ('Blues', 'PERSON'), ('Manchester United', 'ORG'), ('Chiesa', 'GPE'), ('Salisu', 'PERSON'), ('Around 70%', 'PERCENT'), ('Mississippi', 'GPE'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('five', 'CARDINAL'), ('Dynamo Dresden', 'ORG'), ('second', 'ORDINAL'), ('German Football', 'ORG'), ('two-week', 'DATE'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('1500', 'CARDINAL'), ('8 May 1945', 'DATE'), ('British', 'NORP'), ('Winston Churchill', 'PERSON'), ('Europe', 'LOC'), ('BBC Sport', 'ORG'), ('La Liga', 'PERSON'), ('Spain', 'GPE'), ('Britain', 'GPE'), ('Albert Jarrett', 'PERSON'), ('some 10,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('West Indians', 'NORP'), ('Atlantic', 'LOC'), ('Laura Fuchs', 'PERSON'), ('New Yorkers', 'NORP'), ('Tara Reade', 'ORG'), ('New York', 'GPE'), ('Beijing', 'GPE'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Maduro', 'PERSON'), ('Mercedes', 'ORG'), ('Lewis Hamilton', 'PERSON'), ('Formula 1', 'DATE'), ('English', 'LANGUAGE'), ('Indian', 'NORP'), ('Xi Jinping', 'PERSON'), ('millions', 'CARDINAL'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('Corteva Agriscience', 'ORG'), ('Sweden', 'GPE'), ('More than 650,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('Gollum', 'ORG'), ('Tolkien', 'PERSON'), ('one 11-hour', 'TIME'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Leon', 'PERSON'), ('2017', 'DATE'), ('Jamal Khashoggi', 'PERSON'), ('Newcastle United', 'ORG'), ('the Premier League', 'ORG'), ('Berlin', 'GPE'), ('Soviet', 'NORP'), ('2', 'CARDINAL'), ('week', 'DATE'), ('1918', 'DATE'), ('330,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('this year', 'DATE'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Italy', 'GPE'), ('third', 'ORDINAL'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('Hawaii', 'GPE'), ('this week', 'DATE'), ('Robin Sinha', 'PERSON'), ('Walthamstow', 'GPE'), ('London', 'GPE'), ("BBC Sport's", 'ORG'), ('Quarantine Quiz', 'PERSON'), ('Chris Hughes', 'PERSON'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Liam Loftus', 'PERSON'), ('Three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Muslims', 'NORP'), ('Ramadan', 'PERSON'), ('San Francisco', 'GPE'), ('Tesla', 'ORDINAL'), ('Elon Musk', 'ORG'), ('California', 'GPE'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Britain', 'GPE'), ('Almost a third', 'CARDINAL'), ('British', 'NORP'), ('African', 'NORP'), ('25 years', 'DATE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('10-year', 'DATE'), ('earth', 'LOC'), ('mid-March', 'DATE'), ('Jose Mourinho', 'PERSON'), ('Tanguy Ndombele', 'PERSON'), ('half', 'CARDINAL'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('Indonesian', 'NORP'), ('Australians', 'NORP'), ('Harlem', 'LOC'), ('four', 'CARDINAL'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('14', 'CARDINAL'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('164', 'CARDINAL'), ('Italy', 'GPE'), ('Río Tinto', 'PERSON'), ('Spain', 'GPE'), ('Mars', 'LOC'), ('this week', 'DATE'), ('Their day to day', 'DATE'), ('America', 'GPE'), ('Katty Kay', 'PERSON'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('Tiger Woods', 'PERSON'), ("next week's", 'DATE'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Quinnen Williams', 'PERSON'), ('New York Jets', 'GPE'), ("New York's", 'GPE'), ('LaGuardia Airport', 'FAC'), ('25p', 'CARDINAL'), ("Manu Tuilagi's", 'PERSON'), ('England', 'GPE'), ('Six Nations', 'ORG'), ('Wales', 'GPE'), ('Eddie Jones', 'PERSON'), ('One', 'CARDINAL'), ('Queensland', 'GPE'), ('night', 'TIME'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('England', 'GPE'), ('Manu Tuilagi', 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('four years', 'DATE'), ('third', 'ORDINAL'), ('Wales', 'GPE'), ('64-year-old', 'DATE'), ('Glasgow', 'GPE'), ('30-year-old', 'DATE'), ('County Antrim', 'PERSON'), ('Don Carlo', 'PERSON'), ('1998', 'DATE'), ('this week', 'DATE'), ('Abdul Kareem al-Selwady', 'PERSON'), ('Mixed Martial Arts World Lightweight Champion', 'ORG'), ('2018', 'DATE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Palestinian', 'NORP'), ('Celtic', 'NORP'), ('Aberdeen', 'GPE'), ('Hamilton', 'PERSON'), ('St Johnstone', 'PERSON'), ('more than a decade', 'DATE'), ('Thouria', 'DATE'), ('Greek', 'NORP'), ('Carl Goldman', 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Saturday', 'DATE'), ('Greece', 'GPE'), ('Barcelona', 'ORG'), ('La Liga', 'GPE'), ('Turkey', 'GPE'), ('Greece', 'GPE'), ('EU', 'ORG'), ('The Duchess of Sussex', 'ORG'), ("International Women's Day", 'EVENT'), ('Jurgen Klopp', 'PERSON'), ('Liverpool', 'GPE'), ('Bournemouth', 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('30 years', 'DATE'), ('Austin', 'GPE'), ('Texas', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('34-year', 'DATE'), ('Sean Dyche', 'ORG'), ('Burnley', 'PERSON'), ('Tottenham', 'PERSON'), ('Games', 'PERSON'), ('Kurt Fenech', 'PERSON'), ('Heather', 'PERSON'), ("Ivan Morison's", 'PERSON'), ('New Zealand', 'GPE'), ('fourth', 'ORDINAL'), ('Nevada', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('13-year-old', 'DATE'), ('Virginia', 'GPE'), ('the Red Planet', 'LOC'), ('5%', 'PERCENT'), ('VAT', 'ORG'), ('January', 'DATE'), ('Latifa', 'PERSON'), ('Quanzhou', 'GPE'), ('Alisson', 'PERSON'), ('Wednesday', 'DATE'), ('Champions League', 'ORG'), ('last-16 second', 'DATE'), ('Atletico Madrid', 'PERSON'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Cumbria', 'GPE'), ('BBC Radio Cumbria', 'ORG'), ('Saturday', 'DATE'), ('EFL', 'ORG'), ('Cheryl', 'PERSON'), ('Paul Molesky', 'PERSON'), ('a month', 'DATE'), ('dozens', 'CARDINAL'), ('Crown', 'ORG'), ('Prince Mohammed bin Salman', 'PERSON'), ('2017', 'DATE'), ("Lydia O'Sullivan", 'PERSON'), ('Syria', 'GPE'), ('thousands', 'CARDINAL'), ('Turkey', 'GPE'), ('Greece', 'GPE'), ('Manmohan Singh', 'PERSON'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('Barbara Martin', 'PERSON'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('the early 1960s', 'DATE'), ('the past seven days', 'DATE'), ('Liz Rose', 'PERSON'), ('17 years', 'DATE'), ("Chris Jericho's", 'PERSON'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('US Democratic', 'NORP'), ('Afghanistan', 'GPE'), ('at least 32', 'CARDINAL'), ('Middlesbrough', 'ORG'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Adam Fleming', 'PERSON'), ('60 year', 'DATE'), ('Melodifestivalen', 'ORG'), ('Abba', 'PERSON'), ('Loreen', 'PERSON'), ('Mans Zelmerlow', 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('BBC Tees', 'ORG'), ('Paris', 'GPE'), ('Ligue 1', 'EVENT'), ('Strasbourg', 'GPE'), ('Saturday', 'DATE'), ('Aurat', 'ORG'), ('March', 'DATE'), ('New Zealander Troy Collings', 'ORG'), ('North Korea', 'GPE'), ('England', 'GPE'), ('Wales', 'GPE'), ('the Triple Crown at Twickenham', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Manu Tuilagi', 'PERSON'), ('PM Hassan Diab', 'PERSON'), ('1', 'MONEY'), ('One', 'CARDINAL'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Turkey', 'GPE'), ('Erdogan', 'PERSON'), ('Syria', 'GPE'), ('Burnley entertain Tottenham', 'ORG'), ('Premier League', 'ORG'), ('Liverpool', 'GPE'), ('25', 'CARDINAL'), ('Bournemouth', 'PERSON'), ('27-year-old', 'DATE'), ('Ukrainian', 'NORP'), ('18', 'CARDINAL'), ('Moscow', 'GPE'), ('One', 'CARDINAL'), ('Adele McCormick', 'PERSON'), ('the University of Westminster', 'ORG'), ('Justin Rowlatt', 'PERSON'), ('Antarctica', 'LOC'), ('Ross Sea', 'LOC'), ("Martin Andersen's", 'ORG'), ('Tottenham Hotspur Football Club', 'ORG'), ('14-day', 'DATE'), ('Mumbai', 'GPE'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Universe', 'ORG'), ('Italy', 'GPE'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('Maltese', 'NORP'), ('Turkey', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Syrian', 'NORP'), ('Moscow', 'GPE'), ('Facebook', 'ORG'), ('later this month', 'DATE'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Mark Meadows', 'PERSON'), ('Mulvaney', 'PERSON'), ('Northern Ireland', 'GPE'), ('17-year-old', 'DATE'), ('Joseph McCann', 'PERSON'), ('Michael Oluronbi', 'PERSON'), ('34 years', 'DATE'), ('Corteva Agriscience', 'ORG'), ('Tehran', 'GPE'), ('almost 6,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('145', 'CARDINAL'), ('100,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('233', 'CARDINAL'), ('14', 'CARDINAL'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Braille', 'GPE'), ('Lionel Messi', 'PERSON'), ('Barcelona', 'GPE'), ('Sociedad', 'GPE'), ('La Liga', 'PERSON'), ('just weeks', 'DATE'), ('Alun Wyn Jones', 'PERSON'), ('England', 'GPE'), ('Joe Marler', 'PERSON'), ('Wales', 'ORG'), ('Chinese', 'NORP'), ('Brazilian', 'NORP'), ('Paraguay', 'GPE'), ('Gilbert Khoo', 'PERSON'), ('Heathrow Airport', 'FAC'), ('Turkey', 'GPE'), ('Erdogan', 'PERSON'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Vladimir Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Syria', 'GPE'), ('A quarter', 'CARDINAL'), ('Italy', 'GPE'), ('Friedrich Karl Berger', 'PERSON'), ('94', 'DATE'), ('Germany', 'GPE'), ('25 years', 'DATE'), ("Alanis Morissette's", 'PERSON'), ('Jagged Little Pill', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('October last year', 'DATE'), ('22,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('Brexit', 'GPE'), ('England', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Priyanka Bhatia', 'PERSON'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('At least 23', 'CARDINAL'), ('more than 30', 'CARDINAL'), ('São Paulo', 'GPE'), ('Rio de Janeiro', 'GPE'), ('Hachette', 'ORG'), ('49', 'CARDINAL'), ('daily', 'DATE'), ('second', 'ORDINAL'), ('Eight', 'CARDINAL'), ('Cameron Laux', 'PERSON'), ('South Africa', 'GPE'), ('Armand Duplantis', 'ORG'), ('6', 'CARDINAL'), ('Rory Cellan-Jones', 'PERSON'), ('Each week', 'DATE'), ('Bashir Dokhov', 'PERSON'), ('American', 'NORP'), ('Christian Coleman', 'PERSON'), ('60', 'CARDINAL'), ('the USATF Indoor Championships', 'FAC'), ('New Mexico', 'GPE'), ('33,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('at least a century old', 'DATE'), ("Harvey Weinstein's", 'ORG'), ('seven months in 2012 to 2013', 'DATE'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Elena Chernyshova', 'ORG'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Liverpool', 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('30 years', 'DATE'), ('Jurgen Klopp', 'PERSON'), ("Sadio Mane's", 'ORG'), ('London', 'GPE'), ('16 to 19', 'DATE'), ('Dozens', 'CARDINAL'), ('Pete Buttigieg', 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Democratic', 'NORP'), ('England', 'GPE'), ('second', 'ORDINAL'), ('T20', 'GPE'), ('South Africa', 'GPE'), ('Paris', 'GPE'), ('4', 'CARDINAL'), ('Amiens', 'FAC'), ('3', 'CARDINAL'), ('Mark Zuckerberg', 'PERSON'), ('a week', 'DATE'), ('29', 'CARDINAL'), ('Three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Pakistani', 'NORP'), ('Afghanistan', 'GPE'), ('recent weeks', 'DATE'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Iranian', 'NORP'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Sergio Camargo', 'PERSON'), ('Italian', 'NORP'), ('Sydney', 'GPE'), ('millions', 'CARDINAL'), ('NBA', 'ORG'), ('All-Star MVP Award', 'PRODUCT'), ('LA Lakers', 'ORG'), ('Kobe Bryant', 'PERSON'), ('Riek Machar', 'PERSON'), ("Salva Kiir's", 'PERSON'), ("the European Research Council's", 'ORG'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('five years', 'DATE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('more than a', 'CARDINAL'), ('Chinese', 'NORP'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Asia', 'LOC'), ('the first half of 2020', 'DATE'), ('Extinction Rebellion', 'ORG'), ('French', 'NORP'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Mexico', 'GPE'), ('50 tonnes', 'QUANTITY'), ('Two', 'CARDINAL'), ('British', 'NORP'), ('Colombia', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('11', 'CARDINAL'), ('England', 'GPE'), ('223', 'CARDINAL'), ('South Africa', 'GPE'), ('third', 'ORDINAL'), ('2', 'CARDINAL'), ('2019', 'DATE'), ('Year after', 'DATE'), ('year', 'DATE'), ('Vanuatu', 'ORG'), ('Earth', 'LOC'), ('Stephen Kelly', 'PERSON'), ('Love Island', 'LOC'), ('London', 'GPE'), ('Wang Yi', 'PERSON'), ('EU', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Scotch', 'NORP'), ('Mark Zuckerberg', 'PERSON'), ('Europe', 'LOC'), ('Mali', 'PERSON'), ('Islamic', 'NORP'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Benjamin Griveaux', 'PERSON'), ('Paris', 'GPE'), ('more than 100 years', 'DATE'), ('Mario', 'PERSON'), ('Arthur Avenue', 'FAC'), ('New York’s', 'GPE'), ('Italian', 'NORP'), ('Bernie Sanders', 'PERSON'), ('Democratic', 'NORP'), ('Lewis Burton', 'PERSON'), ('Love Island', 'LOC'), ('a day', 'DATE'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('just five years', 'DATE'), ("Storm Ciara's", 'ORG'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('Houthi', 'ORG'), ('Saudi Arabia', 'GPE'), ('Wuhan', 'GPE'), ('French Asians', 'NORP'), ('Laura Whitmore', 'PERSON'), ('Caroline Flack', 'PERSON'), ('Alison Rose', 'PERSON'), ('Lottie Davies', 'ORG'), ('England', 'GPE'), ('Scotland', 'GPE'), ('Nwobi Nwakota', 'PERSON'), ('Nigeria', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('the Duchess of Cambridge', 'GPE'), ('Hundreds', 'CARDINAL'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Diamond Princess', 'FAC'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Amazon', 'ORG'), ('72', 'DATE'), ('New Zealand', 'GPE'), ('Arab', 'NORP'), ('Jewish', 'NORP'), ('Ryan', 'ORG'), ('west African', 'NORP'), ('Islamist', 'NORP'), ('recent years', 'DATE'), ('Aston Villa', 'GPE'), ('Dean Smith', 'PERSON'), ('VAR', 'ORG'), ('Tottenham', 'PERSON'), ('Premier League', 'ORG'), ('Villa Park', 'FAC'), ('Sunday', 'DATE'), ('Gharib', 'PERSON'), ('Israeli', 'NORP'), ('Love Island', 'LOC'), ('London', 'GPE'), ('this week', 'DATE'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Universe', 'ORG'), ('24/7', 'CARDINAL'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Bedfordshire', 'GPE'), ('Hertfordshire', 'PERSON'), ('Buckinghamshire', 'PERSON'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Join Jonathan Sutherland', 'PERSON'), ('Steven Thompson', 'PERSON'), ('Malky Mackay', 'PERSON'), ('weekend', 'DATE'), ('Scottish Premiership', 'EVENT'), ('Democrats', 'NORP'), ('Virginia', 'GPE'), ('Jordan', 'GPE'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('more than five tonnes', 'QUANTITY'), ('Comedian Russell Kane', 'PERSON'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('the World Health Organization', 'ORG'), ('Laura Whitmore', 'PERSON'), ('Caroline Flack', 'PERSON'), ('six', 'CARDINAL'), ('the Red Planet', 'LOC'), ('Kenya', 'GPE'), ('three days', 'DATE'), ('205km', 'QUANTITY'), ('Siberia', 'LOC'), ('Lake Baikal', 'LOC'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('French', 'NORP'), ('Emmanuel Macron', 'PERSON'), ('Summia Tora', 'PERSON'), ('returnee Ade Daramy', 'PERSON'), ('Millions', 'CARDINAL'), ('Hubei province', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Voyager', 'PRODUCT'), ('Pale Blue Dot', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Earth', 'LOC'), ('just a couple of months', 'DATE'), ('Chinese', 'NORP'), ('Wuhan', 'GPE'), ('ninth', 'ORDINAL'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Barcelona', 'GPE'), ('La Liga', 'PERSON'), ('Real Madrid', 'PERSON'), ('Getafe', 'PERSON'), ('Chris Brown', 'PERSON'), ('Amber Rose', 'PERSON'), ('Italian', 'NORP'), ('decades', 'DATE'), ('1,500', 'CARDINAL'), ('Ana Viladomiu', 'PERSON'), ('La Pedrera', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Antoni Gaudí', 'PERSON'), ('Barcelona', 'GPE'), ('seventh', 'ORDINAL'), ('Premier League', 'ORG'), ('the season', 'DATE'), ('second-half', 'DATE'), ('Newcastle', 'ORG'), ('Emirates Stadium', 'FAC'), ('Gaborone', 'GPE'), ('Botswana', 'GPE'), ('Love Island', 'LOC'), ('England', 'GPE'), ('2026', 'DATE'), ('A diplomatic row', 'DATE'), ('Huawei', 'ORG'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('5', 'CARDINAL'), ('Wales', 'GPE'), ('England', 'GPE'), ('Swedish', 'NORP'), ('two hours', 'TIME'), ('Newcastle', 'GPE'), ('the Premier League', 'ORG'), ('Tottenham', 'PERSON'), ('Aston Villa', 'GPE'), ('Porto', 'PERSON'), ('Moussa Marega', 'PERSON'), ('Vitoria Guimaraes', 'PERSON'), ('German', 'NORP'), ('the final three months of last year', 'DATE'), ('two-year-old', 'DATE'), ('2016', 'DATE'), ('Ugandan', 'GPE'), ('Swiss', 'NORP'), ('Canadian', 'NORP'), ('NFL', 'ORG'), ('Antonio Brown', 'PERSON'), ('Shanghai', 'GPE'), ('Four', 'CARDINAL'), ('Quebec', 'GPE'), ('Alberta', 'GPE'), ('Canada', 'GPE'), ('London Stadium', 'ORG'), ('West Ham', 'LOC'), ('the FA Cup', 'EVENT'), ('West Brom', 'LOC'), ('naturalist', 'ORG'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('Manchester United', 'ORG'), ('Ole Gunnar Solskjaer', 'PERSON'), ('the Atlantic Ocean', 'LOC'), ('West African', 'NORP'), ('Australian', 'NORP'), ('Edward', 'PERSON'), ('Manchester City', 'GPE'), ('Pep Guardiola', 'PERSON'), ('FA Cup', 'EVENT'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('the Intellectual Property Office', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Senate', 'ORG'), ('Patrick Stewart', 'PERSON'), ('Inter Milan', 'ORG'), ('Christian Eriksen', 'PERSON'), ('Tottenham', 'PERSON'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('OECD', 'ORG'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('Roger Federer', 'PERSON'), ('Australian', 'NORP'), ('John Millman', 'PERSON'), ('Australian', 'NORP'), ('fourth', 'ORDINAL'), ('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('Jose Mourinho', 'PERSON'), ("Inter Milan's", 'ORG'), ('Christian Eriksen', 'PERSON'), ('100 tonnes', 'QUANTITY'), ('the Middle East Institute', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('George Takei', 'PERSON'), ('1960s', 'DATE'), ('Star Trek TV', 'ORG'), ('Sauntore Thomas', 'PERSON'), ('Danfo', 'ORG'), ('South Africa', 'GPE'), ('88', 'CARDINAL'), ('England', 'GPE'), ('312 after two days', 'DATE'), ('fourth', 'ORDINAL'), ('Test', 'EVENT'), ('Johannesburg', 'GPE'), ('today', 'DATE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('treasury', 'ORG'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('this year', 'DATE'), ('hundreds', 'CARDINAL'), ('the last month', 'DATE'), ('BBC Newsnight', 'ORG'), ('Lex Gillies', 'ORG'), ('John Stumpf', 'PERSON'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Terry Jones', 'PERSON'), ('the age of 77', 'DATE'), ('Thailand', 'GPE'), ('94,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('East Africa', 'GPE'), ('Beijing', 'GPE'), ('Ian Siddall', 'PERSON'), ('25,000', 'MONEY'), ('thousands', 'CARDINAL'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('Nick Kyrgios', 'PERSON'), ('Rafael Nadal', 'PERSON'), ('the last 16', 'DATE'), ('the Australian Open', 'EVENT'), ('five', 'CARDINAL'), ('Karen Khachanov', 'PERSON'), ('about one', 'CARDINAL'), ('At least 10', 'CARDINAL'), ('26', 'CARDINAL'), ('Alberta', 'GPE'), ('Canada', 'GPE'), ('31', 'CARDINAL'), ('nearly 40 years', 'DATE'), ('March 2019', 'DATE'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Democratic', 'NORP'), ('YouTube', 'PRODUCT'), ('West', 'LOC'), ('Japan', 'GPE'), ('week', 'DATE'), ('Almost two decades', 'DATE'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('French', 'NORP'), ('Saint-Santin', 'GPE'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Simon', 'PERSON'), ('Garfunkel', 'PERSON'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('the 1970s', 'DATE'), ('this week', 'DATE'), ('Journalist Sajid Mir', 'PERSON'), ('hours', 'TIME'), ('Pakistan', 'GPE'), ('Kashmir', 'LOC'), ('Mexico', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Michy Batshuayi', 'PERSON'), ('Fikayo Tomori', 'ORG'), ('half', 'CARDINAL'), ('Chelsea', 'ORG'), ('FA Cup', 'ORG'), ('fifth', 'ORDINAL'), ('hundreds', 'CARDINAL'), ('37th', 'ORDINAL'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Canada', 'GPE'), ('Saturday', 'DATE'), ('Chinese', 'NORP'), ('Florida', 'GPE'), ('Thelma Schoonmaker', 'PERSON'), ('Scorsese', 'ORG'), ('Netflix', 'PERSON'), ('Australian', 'NORP'), ("Serena Williams'", 'PERSON'), ('Wang Qiang', 'PERSON'), ('the Australian Open', 'EVENT'), ('BBC Sport', 'ORG'), ('Grand Slam', 'EVENT'), ('American', 'NORP'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('England', 'GPE'), ('Ben Stokes', 'PERSON'), ('fourth', 'ORDINAL'), ('South Africa', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Iranian', 'NORP'), ('Nafiseh Kohnavard', 'PERSON'), ('Marion Cotillard', 'PERSON'), ('Antarctica', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('US Senate', 'ORG'), ('Donald Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Saturday', 'DATE'), ('English Football League', 'ORG'), ('One year', 'DATE'), ('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('Corrego', 'NORP'), ('Gordon Brown', 'PERSON'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('Bombay', 'GPE'), ('Fifteen', 'CARDINAL'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('Lunar New Year', 'EVENT'), ('Philippines', 'GPE'), ('England', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('2016', 'DATE'), ('four', 'CARDINAL'), ('50', 'CARDINAL'), ('a fluctuating first day of the fourth Test', 'DATE'), ('South Africa', 'GPE'), ('Seventeen', 'CARDINAL'), ('Guatemalan', 'GPE'), ('South African', 'NORP'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('millions', 'CARDINAL'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Hundreds of thousands', 'CARDINAL'), ('at least 13', 'CARDINAL'), ('the past seven days', 'DATE'), ('Second', 'ORDINAL'), ('Karolina Pliskova', 'PERSON'), ('fifth', 'ORDINAL'), ('Elina Svitolina', 'PERSON'), ('the Australian Open third round', 'EVENT'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('Lunar New Year', 'EVENT'), ('two hours', 'TIME'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Democrats', 'NORP'), ('Sky Brown', 'PERSON'), ('the Tokyo Olympics', 'EVENT'), ('2020', 'DATE'), ('Britain', 'GPE'), ('summer', 'DATE'), ('Kickasso', 'PERSON'), ('Juventus', 'ORG'), ('Cristiano Ronaldo', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ("David Beckham's", 'PERSON'), ('Ashley Cole', 'PERSON'), ('Justin Timberlake', 'PERSON'), ('Odell Beckham Jr', 'PERSON'), ("BBC Click's", 'ORG'), ('Paul Carter', 'PERSON'), ('week', 'DATE'), ('Steve Bruce', 'PERSON'), ('Newcastle', 'GPE'), ('League One Oxford', 'ORG'), ('fourth', 'ORDINAL'), ('England', 'GPE'), ('Ben Stokes', 'PERSON'), ('15%', 'PERCENT'), ('fourth', 'ORDINAL'), ('South Africa', 'GPE'), ('the International Space Station', 'FAC'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Marc Cieslak', 'PERSON'), ('Watch Dogs:', 'ORG'), ("New Year's", 'EVENT'), ('Anastasia Shevchenko', 'PERSON'), ('a year', 'DATE'), ('Golden', 'GPE'), ('Western Canada', 'ORG'), ('more than a century', 'DATE'), ('Chinese', 'NORP'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('more than 30%', 'PERCENT'), ('the last five years', 'DATE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('Pentagon', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Hagan Homes', 'ORG'), ('Manchester City', 'GPE'), ("the Women's FA Cup", 'EVENT'), ('Prince Charles', 'PERSON'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Mike Pence', 'PERSON'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Matteo Salvini', 'PERSON'), ('African American', 'NORP'), ('Muhammad', 'PERSON'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Chelsea', 'ORG'), ('Saturday', 'DATE'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Universe', 'ORG'), ('Nick Clegg', 'PERSON'), ('WhatsApp', 'ORG'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Highlands', 'GPE'), ('Islands', 'LOC'), ('BBC Radio', 'ORG'), ('Scotland', 'GPE'), ('Turkey', 'GPE'), ('Elazig province', 'GPE'), ('over a thousand', 'CARDINAL'), ('20', 'CARDINAL'), ('last week', 'DATE'), ('Mark Wood', 'PERSON'), ('England', 'GPE'), ('fourth', 'ORDINAL'), ('South Africa', 'GPE'), ('Johannesburg', 'GPE'), ('Rafael Nadal', 'PERSON'), ('Spanish', 'NORP'), ('Pablo Carreno Busta', 'PERSON'), ('Australian', 'NORP'), ('fourth', 'ORDINAL'), ('four', 'CARDINAL'), ('between 2006 and 2015', 'DATE'), ('Wuhan', 'GPE'), ('six days', 'DATE'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('European', 'NORP'), ('British', 'NORP'), ('Chinese', 'NORP'), ('Wuhan', 'GPE'), ('14', 'CARDINAL'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('Meijer Nieweg', 'PERSON'), ('August 1942', 'DATE'), ('Quique Setien', 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Barcelona', 'ORG'), ('Valencia', 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Spanish', 'NORP'), ('Nigeria', 'GPE'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('Vanessa Nakate', 'PERSON'), ('only one', 'CARDINAL'), ('four', 'CARDINAL'), ('Davos', 'ORG'), ('Oxford', 'ORG'), ('Selina Todd', 'PERSON'), ('this week', 'DATE'), ("The London School of Hygiene & Tropical Medicine's", 'ORG'), ('Rosalind Eggo', 'PERSON'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('North Korean', 'NORP'), ('Friends', 'ORG'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('more than 15 years', 'DATE'), ('three hours', 'TIME'), ('Lori Daybell', 'PERSON'), ('Hawaii', 'GPE'), ('1973', 'DATE'), ('the Khmer Rouge', 'ORG'), ('Sussexes', 'PERSON'), ('Edward VIII', 'PERSON'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('American', 'NORP'), ('Canada', 'GPE'), ('two weeks', 'DATE'), ('Americans', 'NORP'), ('the White House', 'FAC'), ('this week', 'DATE'), ('Mecca', 'GPE'), ("Asayel Slay's", 'PERSON'), ('AfD', 'ORG'), ('German', 'NORP'), ('Hanau', 'ORG'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('Arrowe Park', 'GPE'), ('the next 14 days', 'DATE'), ('America', 'GPE'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('Huawei', 'ORG'), ('Joe Biden', 'PERSON'), ('Donald Trump', 'PERSON'), ("BBC Radio 4's", 'ORG'), ("Woman's Hour", 'FAC'), ('this week', 'DATE'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Oxford', 'PERSON'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Oxford', 'PRODUCT'), ('433', 'CARDINAL'), ('French', 'NORP'), ('Emmanuel Macron', 'PERSON'), ('Britain', 'GPE'), ('Barcelona', 'GPE'), ('La Liga', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('London', 'GPE'), ('VAR', 'ORG'), ('the Premier League', 'ORG'), ('Saturday', 'DATE'), ('Chelsea', 'ORG'), ('Frank Lampard', 'PERSON'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('10 years', 'DATE'), ('Cardiff', 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('2010', 'DATE'), ('27', 'CARDINAL'), ('Monrovia', 'GPE'), ('Los Angeles', 'GPE'), ('Jurgen Klopp', 'PERSON'), ('10-year-old', 'DATE'), ('Daragh', 'PERSON'), ('Liverpool', 'PERSON'), ('Chris Morphet', 'PERSON'), ('Fair Isle', 'EVENT'), ('50 years ago', 'DATE'), ('Gabriel Jesus', 'PERSON'), ('80th-minute', 'TIME'), ('Manchester City', 'GPE'), ('Leicester', 'GPE'), ('seven', 'CARDINAL'), ('second', 'ORDINAL'), ('six years', 'DATE'), ('some 400,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('Volodymyr Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('seven-day', 'DATE'), ('Steve Coogan', 'PERSON'), ('Tyson Fury', 'ORG'), ('Deontay Wilder', 'PERSON'), ('BBC Sport', 'ORG'), ('Cristiano Ronaldo', 'PERSON'), ('11th', 'ORDINAL'), ('Serie A', 'ORG'), ('1,000th', 'CARDINAL'), ('Juventus', 'ORG'), ('Sweden', 'GPE'), ('One', 'CARDINAL'), ('Indian', 'NORP'), ('Tamil Nadu', 'GPE'), ('hundreds', 'CARDINAL'), ('Unbeaten France', 'ORG'), ('Wales', 'ORG'), ('Cardiff', 'GPE'), ('years', 'DATE'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('three years', 'DATE'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('Sintra', 'ORG'), ('Quinta da Regaleira', 'PERSON'), ('Portugal', 'GPE'), ('Knights Templar', 'ORG'), ('New York', 'GPE'), ('The World Health Organization', 'ORG'), ('Baltimore', 'GPE'), ('ninth', 'ORDINAL'), ('millions', 'CARDINAL'), ('America', 'GPE'), ('Democratic', 'NORP'), ('last month', 'DATE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('2013', 'DATE'), ('Andy', 'PERSON'), ('Owen Farrell', 'PERSON'), ('UCL', 'ORG'), ('nine', 'CARDINAL'), ('about 35', 'CARDINAL'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('16 days', 'DATE'), ('County Cork', 'GPE'), ('Ireland', 'GPE'), ('Matthew Hahn', 'PERSON'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('Australia', 'GPE'), ('17', 'CARDINAL'), ("the Women's T20 World Cup", 'ORG'), ('Sydney', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Finland', 'GPE'), ('Australia', 'GPE'), ('Wales', 'ORG'), ('Wayne Pivac', 'PERSON'), ('Matt Carley', 'PERSON'), ('second-half', 'DATE'), ('27-23', 'CARDINAL'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('Scotland', 'GPE'), ('Rome', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('the Six Nations', 'EVENT'), ("South Africa's", 'GPE'), ('FW de Klerk', 'ORG'), ('Ryanair', 'ORG'), ('Muslim', 'NORP'), ('nine-year-old', 'DATE'), ('Australian', 'NORP'), ('Queensland', 'GPE'), ('Leicester City', 'GPE'), ('Chelsea', 'PERSON'), ('Scotland', 'GPE'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Italy', 'GPE'), ('Rome', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('six', 'CARDINAL'), ('the Six Nations', 'EVENT'), ('Gregor Townsend', 'PERSON'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('North East', 'LOC'), ('Scotland', 'GPE'), ('Orkney', 'PERSON'), ('Shetland', 'PERSON'), ('BBC Radio', 'ORG'), ('Scotland', 'GPE'), ('Nintendo', 'ORG'), ('Animal Crossing', 'ORG'), ('the past seven days', 'DATE'), ('Audie', 'ORG'), ('Alaskan', 'NORP'), ('The World Health Organization', 'ORG'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('This year', 'DATE'), ('São Paulo', 'GPE'), ('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('hundreds', 'CARDINAL'), ('Pep Guardiola', 'PERSON'), ('Raheem Sterling', 'PERSON'), ('Spanish', 'NORP'), ('Real Madrid', 'ORG'), ('Victoria Derbyshire', 'PERSON'), ('The Secret Garden', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('the night', 'TIME'), ('Johor Bahru', 'GPE'), ('Malaysia', 'GPE'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Las Vegas', 'GPE'), ('Deontay Wilder', 'PERSON'), ('Tyson Fury', 'ORG'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Australians', 'NORP'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('CCTV', 'ORG'), ('the M6 Toll', 'PRODUCT'), ('La Liga', 'GPE'), ('nine-month', 'DATE'), ('Democratic', 'NORP'), ('Donald Trump', 'PERSON'), ('November', 'DATE'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ("Women's Cricket", 'ORG'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('more than 1,000 years', 'DATE'), ('Chiba', 'GPE'), ('Japan', 'GPE'), ('eight-million', 'CARDINAL'), ('Hadaka Matsuri', 'PERSON'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('EU', 'ORG'), ('Safiyya Shaikh', 'PERSON'), ('Die', 'PERSON'), ('second', 'ORDINAL'), ('007', 'CARDINAL'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('Brown University', 'ORG'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Universe', 'ORG'), ('Democratic', 'NORP'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Cristiano Ronaldo', 'PERSON'), ('1,000th', 'CARDINAL'), ('Juventus', 'ORG'), ('Saturday', 'DATE'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('Ibrahim AbdulAziz', 'PERSON'), ('fourth', 'ORDINAL'), ('Syria', 'GPE'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Tyson Fury', 'ORG'), ('SugarHill Steward', 'ORG'), ('Andy Lee', 'PERSON'), ('Jacob', 'PERSON'), ('Duran', 'PERSON'), ('Saturday', 'DATE'), ('WBC', 'ORG'), ('Deontay Wilder', 'PERSON'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Mercedes', 'ORG'), ('Kierpacz', 'PRODUCT'), ("L'Arche", 'ORG'), ('Jean Vanier', 'PERSON'), ('last year', 'DATE'), ('decades', 'DATE'), ('Corteva Agriscience', 'ORG'), ('six', 'CARDINAL'), ('the Red Planet', 'LOC'), ('1980', 'DATE'), ('2016', 'DATE'), ('Amazon', 'ORG'), ('Al Pacino', 'FAC'), ('Fuhrer', 'GPE'), ('a year', 'DATE'), ('Ivrea', 'NORP'), ('TripAdvisor', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('half', 'CARDINAL'), ('pre-season', 'DATE'), ('Mercedes', 'ORG'), ('2020', 'DATE'), ('this week', 'DATE'), ('Josipa Lisac', 'PERSON'), ('Croatia', 'GPE'), ('New Zealand', 'GPE'), ('Sri Lanka', 'GPE'), ('seven', 'CARDINAL'), ('West Indies', 'GPE'), ('Thailand', 'GPE'), ('Spain', 'GPE'), ('James Rhodes', 'PERSON'), ('New Mexico', 'GPE'), ('Pretoria Prison', 'FAC'), ('1979', 'DATE'), ('More than 200', 'CARDINAL'), ('South Korea', 'GPE'), ('Zero', 'CARDINAL'), ('Democrats', 'NORP'), ('Donald Trump', 'PERSON'), ('3 November', 'DATE'), ('Australian', 'NORP'), ('Quaden Bayles', 'PERSON'), ('Wells Fargo', 'ORG'), ('Santiago', 'GPE'), ('Chile', 'GPE'), ('11', 'CARDINAL'), ('Canadian', 'NORP'), ('Robertson', 'PERSON'), ('38 days', 'DATE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('America', 'GPE'), ('Border Force', 'ORG'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Ukrainian', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Wednesday', 'DATE'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Merseyside', 'GPE'), ('BBC Radio Merseyside', 'ORG'), ('Serena Williams', 'PERSON'), ('just 43 minutes', 'TIME'), ('Auckland', 'GPE'), ('Two', 'CARDINAL'), ('London Marathon', 'EVENT'), ('London', 'GPE'), ('Wilson Kipsang', 'PERSON'), ('English', 'LANGUAGE'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Arlene Foster', 'PERSON'), ("Michelle O'Neill", 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Northern Ireland', 'GPE'), ('French', 'NORP'), ('Frank Lampard', 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Premier League', 'ORG'), ('the past seven days', 'DATE'), ('week', 'DATE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine International Airlines', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('100%', 'PERCENT'), ('European', 'NORP'), ('Prohibition', 'LOC'), ('Lizzie Siddal', 'PERSON'), ('today', 'DATE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Bianca Andreescu', 'PERSON'), ('Australian', 'NORP'), ('Sussexit', 'ORG'), ('Mid-East', 'LOC'), ('Australian', 'NORP'), ('Harry', 'PERSON'), ('Meghan', 'PERSON'), ('Democrats', 'NORP'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('University of Glasgow', 'ORG'), ('Burns', 'PERSON'), ('Scotland', 'GPE'), ('Wednesday', 'DATE'), ('176', 'CARDINAL'), ('Japan', 'GPE'), ('Nitasha Biswas', 'ORG'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Okinawa', 'ORG'), ('Bush', 'PERSON'), ('Bill Clinton', 'PERSON'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('last year', 'DATE'), ('Arctic sea', 'LOC'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('BBC Radio Northampton', 'ORG'), ('Tehran', 'GPE'), ('Ethiopia', 'GPE'), ('Ethiopia', 'GPE'), ('Sultan Qaboos', 'PERSON'), ('1970', 'DATE'), ('Oman', 'GPE'), ('Greg Abbott', 'PERSON'), ('Buckingham Palace', 'FAC'), ('Prince Harry', 'PERSON'), ('Meghan', 'PERSON'), ('Louisiana', 'GPE'), ('Alabama', 'GPE'), ('Texas', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Western', 'NORP'), ('Iranian', 'NORP'), ("Lou Johnson's", 'PERSON'), ('Motorsport', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('several years', 'DATE'), ('2017', 'DATE'), ('Reynhard Sinaga', 'NORP'), ('Tottenham v Liverpool', 'PERSON'), ('the Premier League', 'ORG'), ('Southampton', 'GPE'), ('Chelsea', 'ORG'), ('Man Utd', 'PERSON'), ('Everton', 'ORG'), ('Scott Derrickson', 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Canadian', 'NORP'), ('Sussexes', 'PERSON'), ('Deepika Padukone', 'PERSON'), ('five years', 'DATE'), ('Iranian', 'NORP'), ('Boeing', 'ORG'), ('737', 'CARDINAL'), ('Max', 'PRODUCT'), ('Alliance', 'ORG'), ('Naomi Long', 'PERSON'), ('Southampton', 'ORG'), ('Ralph Hasenhuttl', 'PERSON'), ('9', 'CARDINAL'), ('Leicester', 'GPE'), ('October', 'DATE'), ('Saints', 'ORG'), ('King Power Stadium', 'FAC'), ('Cristiano Ronaldo', 'PERSON'), ('Inter', 'NORP'), ('Serie A', 'ORG'), ('Manchester United', 'ORG'), ('Romelu Lukaku', 'PERSON'), ('Italy', 'GPE'), ('Sandringham', 'GPE'), ('Monday', 'DATE'), ('Prince Harry', 'PERSON'), ('Meghan', 'PERSON'), ('Rafael Nadal', 'PERSON'), ('Novak Djokovic', 'PERSON'), ('Spain', 'GPE'), ('Serbia', 'GPE'), ('ATP Cup', 'ORG'), ('Sydney', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Tehran', 'GPE'), ('British', 'NORP'), ('170', 'CARDINAL'), ('Billie Eilish', 'PERSON'), ('Lewis Capaldi', 'PERSON'), ('Sheffield United', 'PERSON'), ('West Ham', 'LOC'), ('fifth', 'ORDINAL'), ('The Law Commission', 'ORG'), ('Sony', 'ORG'), ('Samsung', 'ORG'), ('LG', 'ORG'), ('Las Vegas', 'GPE'), ('Swedish', 'NORP'), ('4%', 'PERCENT'), ('2019', 'DATE'), ('Swedavia', 'GPE'), ('the day', 'DATE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('the Middle East', 'LOC'), ('Australia', 'GPE'), ('Shane Warne', 'ORG'), ('one million Australian dollars', 'MONEY'), ('528,514', 'MONEY'), ('Five hundred years', 'DATE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Canadian', 'NORP'), ('Mr Trudeau', 'PERSON'), ('Arguedas Ortiz', 'PERSON'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('San Francisco', 'GPE'), ('Minnesota Vikings', 'ORG'), ('NFL', 'ORG'), ('at least six', 'CARDINAL'), ('Mike Pence', 'PERSON'), ('Americans', 'NORP'), ('today', 'DATE'), ('Mikuru Suzuki', 'PRODUCT'), ('BDO World Darts Championship', 'ORG'), ('four', 'CARDINAL'), ('Lisa Ashton', 'PERSON'), ('Canada', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Boris Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('2020', 'DATE'), ('EU Commission', 'ORG'), ('Takumi Minamino', 'PERSON'), ('Premier League', 'ORG'), ('Liverpool', 'GPE'), ("Lisa Lloyd's", 'PERSON'), ('Mexico', 'GPE'), ('Popocatépetl', 'ORG'), ('3,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('9,800ft', 'QUANTITY'), ('Donald Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Iranian', 'NORP'), ('Himalayas', 'ORG'), ('Everest', 'LOC'), ('Emily Townsend', 'ORG'), ("News Corp's", 'ORG'), ('the Supreme Court', 'ORG'), ('Zlatan', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('AC Milan', 'ORG'), ('The US State Department', 'ORG'), ('Anne Sacoolas', 'PERSON'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('Meghan', 'PERSON'), ('Harry', 'PERSON'), ('Buckingham Palace', 'FAC'), ('centuries', 'DATE'), ('Japanese', 'NORP'), ('San Francisco', 'GPE'), ('49ers', 'CARDINAL'), ('the Minnesota Vikings', 'ORG'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Super Bowl 54', 'EVENT'), ('eBay', 'ORG'), ('Australia', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Sydney airport', 'FAC'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Samira Ahmed', 'PERSON'), ('Barcelona', 'PERSON'), ('Luis Suarez', 'PERSON'), ('four months', 'DATE'), ('Arab', 'NORP'), ('Friday', 'DATE'), ('Tehran', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ("North Korea's", 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Ukrainian', 'NORP'), ('Australia', 'GPE'), ('100-year-old', 'DATE'), ('NFL', 'ORG'), ('Osi Umenyiora', 'PERSON'), ('Jason Bell', 'PERSON'), ('The US Navy', 'ORG'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('the USS Farragut', 'PRODUCT'), ('the Arabian Sea', 'LOC'), ('Hundreds', 'CARDINAL'), ('British', 'NORP'), ('this weekend', 'DATE'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Universe', 'ORG'), ('Across Canada', 'ORG'), ('63', 'CARDINAL'), ('Canadians', 'NORP'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Flight PS752', 'PRODUCT'), ('CES', 'ORG'), ('Marcus Rashford marks', 'PERSON'), ('200th', 'ORDINAL'), ('Manchester United', 'ORG'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Norwich', 'PERSON'), ('Kati Pohler', 'PERSON'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('three days old', 'DATE'), ('Tsai Ing-wen', 'PERSON'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('Taiwan', 'GPE'), ('this weekend', 'DATE'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('Saturday', 'DATE'), ('Premier League', 'ORG'), ('Crystal Palace', 'ORG'), ('Arsenal', 'ORG'), ('almost four years', 'DATE'), ('145,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('last month', 'DATE'), ('a year', 'DATE'), ('Canadians', 'NORP'), ('Canada', 'GPE'), ('this week', 'DATE'), ('Tsai Ing-wen', 'PERSON'), ('Han Kuo-yu', 'PERSON'), ('Taiwanese-Chinese', 'NORP'